<Session title="HISTORY.BMG">
  <Sentence id="0">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Two years ago, just before her 14th birthday, Ashley[0]received a letter which came with a handheld device[1]with three letters on it - 'DAS'. What was even stranger[2]was that the letter was from her father, who she had[3]believed to be dead.[4]Her aunt Jessica, who raised Ashley from the age of[5]three, had told Ashley that her parents died in an[6]accident while they were researching memory at[7]MJ Labs. After seeing the letter, Jessica admitted to[8]Ashley that her father was still alive and that he was[9]waiting for Ashley to come to him.[10] [11]Discovering that her father was alive, Ashley set off[12]with her aunt to Blood Edward Island. While trying to[13]meet her father, she also discovered the truth about[14]the Another system that her parents had risked their[15]lives for...and about her mother's death.[16] [17]A year later, Richard started to work for JC Valley[18]Technology, a laboratory located by Lake Juliet. But[19]despite his promise to Ashley, he has stopped coming[20]home at weekends...[21] [22]</Original>
    <Translation>两年前,就在阿修蕾14岁生日之前,[0]她收到了一封信.伴随而来的还有一个写着'DAS'的机器[1]更奇怪的是,[2]这封信来自她一直以为已经去世了的[3]爸爸.[4]从三岁就开始抚养着阿修蕾的姑姑,杰西卡.[5]一直告诉她她的父母在MJ实验室研究记忆时的[6]一次事故中已经丧生了.[7]看到这封信之后,[8]杰西卡向阿修蕾承认了她的父亲还活着并且[9]在某个地方等着她.[10] [11]得知爸爸还活着以后, [12]阿修蕾和姑姑出发前往布拉德爱德华岛. [13]去见爸爸的过程中, 她还发现了[14]父母冒着生命危险保护的Another系统...[15]和妈妈去世的真相.[16] [17]一年后, 理查德开始为一个坐落在朱丽叶湖附近的实验室[18], JC山谷科技公司工作.[19]尽管向阿修蕾作了保证, [20]他还是没能履行每个周末回家的承诺...[21] [22]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="1">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Right at the end of her summer holidays, Ashley [0]received an invitation to a family camp from her[1]father, Richard, who she hadn't seen in six months.[2]With it came a new DAS model.[3] [4]Jessica pressured her into going, but as soon as Ashley[5]got off the bus at Lake Juliet, her bag was stolen.[6]Although she was already regretting coming, Ashley[7]had no money for the bus home and thus she had no[8]option but to search for Richard's campsite.[9] [10]As she set off to find him, a message from Richard[11]arrived on the DAS - "Go ahead and check in at the[12]guesthouse." But when Ashley found the guesthouse, it[13]was closed. She met Dan, a Forest Ranger, while trying[14]to find the campsite staff. Dan informed her that the[15]staff were prone to taking breaks and told her about[16]recent events at Lake Juliet. He also promised to look[17]out for her stolen bag...[18] [19]</Original>
    <Translation>就在暑假的尾声,  [0]阿修蕾收到了她的爸爸理查德发来的家庭露营的邀请,[1]这时她已经有6个月没有见到她的爸爸了.[2]同时阿修蕾还收到了新型号的DAS.[3] [4]杰西卡催促阿修蕾赶快出发,但是就在她刚到朱丽叶湖 [5]走下巴士的时候, 包却被人偷走了.[6]尽管心里满腹怨言,[7]已经没钱坐车回去的阿修蕾[8]不得不开始寻找爸爸的营地.[9] [10]就在她开始去找爸爸的时候, DAS上收到了爸爸[11]理查德发来的信息 - "向前走到商店那里登记." [12]但当阿修蕾来到商店的时候, 却发现商店门是关的[13]她在寻找营地工作人员的时候, 遇到了护林员丹.[14]丹告诉她,营地工作人员经常会溜出去一会,[15]并告诉他朱丽叶湖最近发生的一些事情. [16]他还承诺会帮助寻找[17]阿修蕾失窃的背包...[18] [19]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="2">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley returned to the guesthouse and found it open.[0]There, she met a young man by the name of Tommy,[1]who appeared from the store room and helped Ashley[2]check in. She received an ID card, which not only let her[3]into the campsite but also allowed her to buy items[4]from the guesthouse shop.[5] [6]Tommy helped her to file a police report for her stolen [7]bag, and also told her about the fire at the villa and [8]the thefts from the store room.[9]Ashley was disappointed to hear that she and her [10]father were the only ones at the family camp. Tommy[11]went on to tell her about the mysterious camper in a[12]suit and the Rainbow Stone in the guesthouse.[13] [14]As Ashley went through the gate to find Richard's [15]campsite, a memory of her mother standing before [16]those same gates suddenly resurfaced.[17]Disoriented by this sudden recollection, Ashley made[18]her way to her father's campsite...[19] [20]</Original>
    <Translation>阿修蕾回到商店,发现商店已经开门.[0]她在那儿见到了汤米,[1]他从储藏室出来并帮助阿修蕾完成了登记 [2]阿修蕾得到了一张[3]能够让她进入营地[4]还能在商店购买东西的ID卡.[5] [6]汤米为她丢失的背包填写了一份报案记录,[7]并告诉她一些关于别墅失火和 [8]储藏室遇到小偷的事情.[9]阿修蕾得知她和她的父亲是这次家庭露营的唯一 [10]参与者, 感到很是失望. [11]汤米还介绍了关于穿西装的神秘露营者[12]和商店的彩虹石的事情.[13] [14]就在阿修蕾穿过大门寻找理查德的营地的时候, [15]一段关于她的妈妈站在这门前的记忆[16]突然在脑海闪现.[17]恍恍惚惚中,[18]她走向了爸爸的营地...[19] [20]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="3">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After six months apart, Ashley found it hard to talk[0]to her father. After he realised that he had forgotten[1]the charcoal for the barbecue, Ashley snapped and told[2]him that she didn't want to be at the camp. She also[3]told him about her dream of becoming a musician.[4]Shaken by what his daughter had to say, Richard[5]finally told Ashley why he had invited her to Lake[6]Juliet. [7] [8]While working at JC Valley, Richard found out that [9]Sayoko visited the lab 13 years ago in secret, and that[10]the reason behind her visit had something to do with[11]Another. This was the first time since returning from[12]Blood Edward Island that Richard and Ashley had[13]spoken about Sayoko's death and about the[14]development of Another.[15] [16]Richard gave Ashley the TAS, a device invented by [17]Sayoko, which unexpectedly responded to Ashley's[18]touch and activated. Richard let her keep it after she[19]promised not to show it to anyone. In return, she gave[20]him Sayoko's pendant, the only keepsake of her mother[21]that she had.[22] [23]Interrupted by Richard's stomach growling, Ashley[24]went back to the guesthouse for some charcoal...[25] [26]</Original>
    <Translation>6个月之后的重逢,阿修蕾发现很难和爸爸[0]再有多少共同语言. [1]在理查德意识到他忘带了烧烤的木炭后,阿修蕾再忍不住 [2]说出她根本不想来这个露营. [3]她告诉爸爸自己对于音乐的梦想.[4]震惊于女儿的言语,理查德最终[5]告诉了阿修蕾邀请她来朱丽叶湖的[6]真正原因. [7] [8]在JC山谷工作期间, 理查德发现沙夜子曾 [9]在13年前秘密来过这个实验室, [10]并且她来这里的原因和Another有关 [11]这是从布拉德爱德华岛回来之后[12]理查德和阿修蕾第一次[13]谈起关于沙夜子的死和[14]Another的开发.[15] [16]理查德把沙夜子发明的TAS交给阿修蕾,[17]阿修蕾的触摸竟意外地激活了这个装置.[18]在阿修蕾保证不让别人看到TAS之后,[19]理查德同意让她带着TAS. 作为报答,[20]阿修蕾把妈妈的唯一纪念 --沙夜子的挂饰-- 交給[21]了爸爸.[22] [23]理查德饿着的肚子开始作响,[24]阿修蕾立刻回到商店去取木炭...[25] [26]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="4">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley returned to the guesthouse to get some[0]charcoal, but in the store room she saw a big dog and[1]a boy clutching a teddy bear.  Realising that it was her[2]teddy bear, Ashley pursued them out through the back[3]of the storage room. However, thanks to the dog, the[4]boy managed to escape. Tommy then showed up and[5]accused Ashley of being responsible for the thefts[6]from the storage room. After proving her innocence,[7]Ashley finally managed to get some charcoal.[8] [9]Tommy also showed her a photo of the villa that had[10]been burned down three days ago. As soon as she saw[11]it, Ashley once again had a vivid flashback of her[12]mother - standing in front of that same villa.[13]On her way back to the campsite, she ran into Richard,[14]who had to return to the lab urgently.[15] [16]Before rushing off, Richard told her that Gina, someone[17]from JC Valley, would come and have the barbecue with[18]her. So, Ashley was left in the campsite all alone...[19]</Original>
    <Translation>阿修蕾回到商店去取木炭,[0]却在储藏室看见了一只大狗和拿着泰迪熊[1]的小男孩.  意识到那是自己的泰迪熊之后,[2]阿修蕾追赶着他们走出了储藏室的后门.[3]可是,因为那只狗, 小男孩[4]成功地逃脱了. 然后汤米出现了,[5]他指责阿修蕾要为储藏室失窃的事情负责.[6]在证明了自己的清白后,[7]阿修蕾终于拿到了木炭.[8] [9]汤米还向阿修蕾展示了3天前被烧毁的[10]别墅的照片. 就在阿修蕾看到照片的时候,[11]关于妈妈的记忆又鲜活地闪现在她脑海[12]-妈妈正站在那别墅前面.[13]在回营地的路上, 她遇到了正急匆匆[14]赶回实验室的理查德.[15] [16]离开前, 理查德告诉阿修蕾JC山谷的吉娜[17]会过来和她一起烧烤.[18]这样,阿修蕾又被单独留在了营地...[19]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="5">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="6">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="7">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="8">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="9">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="10">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Richard's colleague, Ryan, came to the campsite instead[0]of Gina. Ashley was certain she'd seen him somewhere[1]before. Ryan told her that she looked like her mother, [2]Sayoko, and talked about his experiences of working [3]with her. Ashley was enjoying the barbecue with Ryan, [4]but Elizabeth suddenly appeared and dragged him off to [5]help her look for her lost music player.[6] [7]Alone yet again, Ashley received a message on the[8]DAS from her father - "Can you get my backpack and[9]bring it back to the cottage for me, please?"[10]She took his backpack and started off for the cottage,[11]but was stopped by Dan on the way. He showed her[12]a photo of a missing child, who was none other than[13]the boy Ashley had seen in the guesthouse.[14] [15]Ashley bumped into Ryan and Elizabeth at a vacant [16]campsite, still looking for the lost music player. Before[17]leaving, Ryan told Ashley that he hoped they could [18]meet again. On the way to the lake shore, Ashley [19]spotted Matthew, but when she called out to him, he [20]ran away.[21]Chasing after him, she arrived at a run-down shack.[22] [23]</Original>
    <Translation>理查德的同事莱恩代替吉娜来到了营地.[0]阿修蕾确信自己曾在什么地方见过莱恩.[1]莱恩告诉阿修蕾她很象她的母亲沙夜子, [2]还和她分享自己和沙夜子一起工作的经历.[3]正当阿修蕾高兴地和莱恩一起烧烤的时候, [4]伊丽莎白突然出现拉走了莱恩[5]要他帮她寻找丢失的播放器.[6] [7]再次一个人的阿修蕾在DAS上收到了[8]爸爸的信息- "你能拿上我的背包,把它[9]带到小屋来吗?"[10]阿修蕾带着背包开始前往小屋,[11]中途遇见了丹. 他給她看了一个[12]走失的孩子的照片, [13]这正是她在商店看到的哪个男孩.[14] [15]阿修蕾路过一个空营地的时候又撞见[16]还在寻找播放器的莱恩和伊丽莎白. [17]离开前,莱恩告诉阿修蕾希望还能再次见到.[18]在去湖边的路上, 阿修蕾 [19]见到了马修, 但当她想喊住他的时候,  [20]马修跑开了.[21]阿修蕾追逐着马修来到了一个破陋的小屋.[22] [23]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="11">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley investigated the shack, but couldn't find anyone[0]there. Around the back, she found her teddy bear next[1]to an old well. She then rescued Matthew, who was[2]trapped inside the well. [3] [4]Matthew told Ashley he found her bear at the burned[5]villa, and that her bag was also there. Ashley asked [6]him why he ran away from home and he explained that[7]he was looking for clues to find his father, who was[8]kidnapped five years ago and was still missing. When[9]Ashley expressed some doubt, he ran away. Ashley[10]went to the villa remains, where she found her band[11]scores.[12] [13]Matthew then appeared and Ashley told him about[14]her mother having been shot dead. Hearing that,[15]Matthew admitted that he had lied about his father[16]being kidnapped, but not about his disappearance. As[17]she headed to her father's cottage again, Ashley met[18]Tommy and his friend Sam, and learned that the old[19]burned villa had belonged to Judd Fitzgerald, former[20]head of JC Valley. She also found out that Tommy,[21]Sam and Elizabeth were in a band, and planning to[22]enter the same contest she was interested in.[23] [24]</Original>
    <Translation>阿修蕾调查了这个小屋,却找不到任何人.[0]在小屋后面的老井旁, 她发现了她的泰迪熊.[1]接着她救出了[2]被困在井里的马修. [3] [4]马修告诉阿修蕾他是在烧毁的别墅发现的[5]她的泰迪小熊,她的背包也在那里. [6]阿修蕾问他为什么离家出走, 他解释说[7]是为了去寻找能找到5年前被绑架[8]至今下落不明的爸爸的线索. [9]当阿修蕾提出了一些怀疑,他再次跑开了. [10]阿修蕾来到别墅废墟, [11]找到了她的乐谱.[12] [13]这是马修出现了,阿修蕾告诉他[14]自己的妈妈被枪击身亡. 听到这里,[15]马修承认了自己的爸爸并没有被绑架,[16]但确实是失踪了. [17]再次回到前往小屋的路上, 阿修蕾[18]遇到了汤米和他的朋友萨姆, 得知被烧毁的别墅[19]属于JC山谷的前任老板贾德·菲茨杰拉德.[20]她还发现汤米,萨姆,和伊丽莎白[21]组建了一个乐队, 也正准备参加[22]她所感兴趣的那个比赛.[23] [24]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="12">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As Ashley hurried to her father's cottage, she found[0]Matthew in front of the disused boathouse. He wanted[1]to go inside to look for clues about his father's[2]disappearance. Ashley tried to talk him out of it by[3]saying it was too dangerous, but ended up going in [4]with him anyway.[5] [6]Sayoko's TAS unlocked the card lock on the door,[7]and they entered the deserted boat house. On the pier[8]behind the boathouse, they saw a bag floating in the[9]lake. Thinking it might be hers, Ashley found some [10]equipment in the boathouse and managed to rope the [11]bag in. It turned out that it wasn't Ashley's bag, but it[12]had once belonged to Matthew's father.[13] [14]Upon opening the lock and looking inside, they found[15]Michael's photo album, a water testing kit, an old[16]floppy disk and Matthew's toy car. Ashley looked at the[17]photos and saw a door with a crest, which she [18]recognised from somewhere.[19] [20]Dan suddenly arrived, and Matthew hid from him [21]behind the door before running off again. Ashley told [22]Dan about the bag she had pulled from the lake, and[23]he noticed that the logo on the floppy disk was the [24]"Crusoe Resort" logo. This was Matthew's father's [25]company, which had gone bankrupt five years ago.[26] [27]Ashley asked Dan where Matthew was found the last[28]time he ran away. After telling Ashley about the old[29]cottage, Dan returned to his patrol, leaving Ashley [30]thinking of her new friend as she held onto his toy car.[31]</Original>
    <Translation>就在阿修蕾赶往父亲的小屋的时候, [0]她发现马修正在一个废弃的船屋前.[1]他想要进去找寻他父亲失踪的线索.[2]阿修蕾想要劝说马修不要进入船屋,[3]却最终也跟他一起[4]走了进去.[5] [6]沙夜子的TAS解开了门上的卡锁,[7]然后他们进入了废弃的船屋.[8]在船屋后的码头上, 他们看见一个浮在湖面上的包裹.[9]觉得可能是自己的背包, 阿修蕾在船屋里[10]找来工具成功地把包裹拉了过来.[11]结果这并不是阿修蕾的背包,[12]而是属于马修的父亲.[13] [14]他们打开上面的锁看了里面, [15]发现了迈克尔的相册, 水质测试剂, 一张旧磁盘[16]和马修的玩具车. 阿修蕾在照片里发现[17]了一个仿佛在哪里见到过的, [18]带有羽冠的大门.[19] [20]丹突然来到这里, 马修躲到了门后,[21]然后再一次跑开. 阿修蕾告诉丹[22]她在湖里拣起一个包,[23]丹注意到磁盘上的标志正是"克鲁索度假村"的标志.[24]这是马修的爸爸的公司,[25]已经在5年前破产了.[26] [27]阿修蕾询问了丹马修上一次出走被发现的地点.[28]丹告诉阿修蕾是一个破旧的小屋,[29]然后回去继续他的巡逻,[30]阿修蕾拿着马修的玩具车思考着如何找到这位新朋友.[31]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="13">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="14">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="15">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="16">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="17">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="18">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="19">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="20">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While Ashley and Matthew were investigating the bag[0]they had pulled in from the lake, Dan arrived and[1]Matthew ran away. Ashley handed the bag over to Dan[2]and went to find Matthew.[3] [4]He was hiding in the basement of an old cottage where[5]a famous photographer used to live, the same place[6]Dan found him last year. Ashley tried to convince him[7]to go back to his uncle's home, but Matthew told her[8]that in September he was being sent to boarding school[9]in England. This was the only chance Matthew had to[10]find his father.[11] [12]As Ashley thought about it, Matthew showed her a[13]treasure map he had drawn the previous year, but the[14]paper had nothing on it. Or so it seemed until Ashley[15]realised it was drawn in invisible ink, and used an[16]electric hotplate to make it legible again. The old[17]hotplate tripped the circuit breaker, leaving both[18]in the dark.[19] [20]Upon getting the lights back on, Ashley found a picture[21]of her parents when they were younger. Empathising[22]with Matthew's wish to find his father, she made a deal[23]with him to look for clues together for just one day.[24] [25]</Original>
    <Translation>在阿修蕾和马修研究从湖里捞上来的包的时候,[0]丹来到这里, 于是马修跑开了.[1]阿修蕾把包交给了丹,[2]然后去寻找马修.[3] [4]马修躲在一个著名的摄像师曾居住的老屋子里,[5]去年丹也是在这个同样的地方找到他的.[6]阿修蕾想要说服他回到他叔叔的家里,[7]但马修告诉她,[8]九月他就要被送到英格兰的寄宿学校.[9]这是他能找到他父亲的[10]最后的机会了.[11] [12]在阿修蕾思考的时候, [13]马修给她看了一张他去年所画的藏宝图,[14]可纸上却什么也没有. [15]阿修蕾意识到这是用隐形墨水画的,[16]使用电烤盘使它再次显现.[17]老旧的电烤盘使电路短路,[18]两人陷入了黑暗之中.[19] [20]当灯再次亮起, [21]阿修蕾发现了一张她父母年轻时的照片.[22]体会到马修想要找到爸爸的急切愿望,[23]她和马修约定在一天之内一起去寻找线索.[24] [25]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="21">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After receiving a message from Richard, Ashley and[0]Matthew went to the covered bridge to meet him.[1]They met Elizabeth on the way, and Ashley told her[2]that her music player was in the shack, but Elizabeth[3]suddenly accused Matthew of stealing it. Richard[4]arrived as they were arguing and seemed to take[5]Elizabeth's side, suspecting Matthew. Ashley lost her[6]temper and argued with Richard, causing Matthew to[7]disappear yet again.[8] [9]After calming down, Richard apologised to Ashley and[10]asked her to bring Matthew to the cottage. Ashley found[11]Matthew crying at the foot of the Lonely Oak. [12]Matthew told her that Richard had reminded him of his[13]father, and he told her about his sister, Kelly. Ashley [14]went and found Matthew's treasure, his last letter from[15]his mother, Emily. He admitted that he'd never talked[16]so much about his parents to anyone before, and[17]Ashley told him that's what friends are for. [18] [19]To prove Matthew's innocence, Ashley went with him to[20]get Elizabeth's music player and the handkerchief it[21]had been wrapped in. It was the same brand as [22]Elizabeth's bandanna. On their way to Richard's [23]cottage, Ashley saw the mysterious man in sunglasses[24]heading for the mermaid statue. She followed him there [25]alone, and he introduced himself as John Smith, a[26]journalist looking into an incident from five years ago.[27]Ashley was unable to get any more information from [28]him, and Mr Smith left without answering any more [29]of her questions.[30] [31]As they hurried on to Richard's cottage, Ashley and[32]Matthew found the bridge gate locked. Ashley asked[33]Matthew to tell no one about the TAS, and she used it[34]to open the card lock and get through the gate.[35] [36]</Original>
    <Translation>收到理查德的信息之后, [0]阿修蕾和马修前往廊桥.[1]他们在路上遇到了伊丽莎白,[2]阿修蕾告诉她在小屋发现了她的播放器, [3]但伊丽莎白指责是马修偷了她的播放器. [4]就在他们争吵时理查德赶到,[5]看起来他也站在伊丽莎白这一边. [6]这让阿修蕾十分生气和理查德争吵起来, [7]这时马修又一次失踪了.[8] [9]冷静下来的理查德向阿修蕾道歉,[10]并要阿修蕾把马修带到小屋来. Ashley found[11]Matthew crying at the foot of the Lonely Oak. [12]Matthew told her that Richard had reminded him of his[13]father, and he told her about his sister, Kelly. Ashley [14]went and found Matthew's treasure, his last letter from[15]his mother, Emily. He admitted that he'd never talked[16]so much about his parents to anyone before, and[17]Ashley told him that's what friends are for. [18] [19]To prove Matthew's innocence, Ashley went with him to[20]get Elizabeth's music player and the handkerchief it[21]had been wrapped in. It was the same brand as [22]Elizabeth's bandanna. On their way to Richard's [23]cottage, Ashley saw the mysterious man in sunglasses[24]heading for the mermaid statue. She followed him there [25]alone, and he introduced himself as John Smith, a[26]journalist looking into an incident from five years ago.[27]Ashley was unable to get any more information from [28]him, and Mr Smith left without answering any more [29]of her questions.[30] [31]As they hurried on to Richard's cottage, Ashley and[32]Matthew found the bridge gate locked. Ashley asked[33]Matthew to tell no one about the TAS, and she used it[34]to open the card lock and get through the gate.[35] [36]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="22">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley and Matthew finally arrived at Richard's [0]cottage, but after Richard apologised to Matthew and [1]started talking with Ashley about Sayoko, he got a[2]call from JC Valley. There was an urgent problem with[3]the security system and he had to go.[4] [5]After Richard left, Ashley used his computer to help [6]Matthew find clues about his father. She found that [7]Michael's company, Crusoe Resort, went bankrupt five [8]years ago, but clues about Michael himself eluded them.[9] [10]Jessica called and admitted she was certain that[11]Richard had invited Ashley to go camping to tell her [12]something about Sayoko. Looking at his computer, [13]Ashley discovered that Richard was investigating the[14]pollution in the lake and that there was more to her[15]mother's death than she had previously realised.[16] [17]Curious to read some of Richard's e-mails, Ashley[18]used the password to open his mail program. After that,[19]she noticed that a new function had been activated on[20]the DAS - "Connect". She could now see feeds from the[21]security cameras. [22] [23]With this, Ashley and Matthew could see the man in[24]sunglasses looking around by the mermaid statue.[25]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="23">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="24">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="25">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="26">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="27">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="28">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="29">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="30">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Having seen what looked like security camera footage[0]on the DAS Connect screen, Ashley went to the [1]mermaid statue to confirm her theory. After that, she[2]tested the water quality of the lake and found that it[3]was being polluted with something. She and Matthew [4]then tested another body of water near the lake. [5] [6]They were interrupted with some good news - Dan had[7]found Ashley's bag. Ashley was happy to have her bag[8]back, but soon discovered her treasured pick case was[9]missing. Eager to find it, Ashley and Matthew set off to[10]the half-built cottage. There, they overheard the[11]mysterious John Smith on a phone call.[12] [13]It seemed he was discussing JC Valley, and also knew[14]something about Crusoe Resort, Matthew's father's[15]company. After leaving a hungry Matthew at the[16]cottage and going back to get her pick case, Ashley[17]walked past the local diner and heard the sound of[18]someone playing an electric guitar.[19] [20]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="31">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The music turned out to be Tommy and Sam practising[0]at the diner. They were rehearsing for a contest they[1]were entering with Elizabeth, the same one that Ashley[2]was planning to enter.[3] [4]Ashley also met Bob, the owner of the diner, who[5]recommended the popular Salmon Rice Burger. Ashley[6]ordered one to take back for Matthew. Waiting, she[7]saw a photo of Bob in front of a hamburger stand - and[8]another memory of her mother resurfaced. Bob told her[9]about how he met a Japanese woman 13 years ago who[10]gave him the idea for the unique Salmon Rice Burger.[11]Ashley had a feeling that it was definitely her mother.[12] [13]Ashley brought the burger back to Matthew at the[14]cottage, and they tidied up the books he had been[15]reading. As they were doing that, Ryan rang the[16]doorbell. Ashley told him that Richard wasn't there, and[17]she was with her friend Matthew. [18] [19]As soon as Ryan heard that Matthew had connections[20]to Crusoe Resort, he told Ashley that she shouldn't[21]associate with him. Then he left, saying that if Ashley[22]wanted to know more about Sayoko or Crusoe Resort,[23]she should come to his cottage where they could speak[24]freely.[25] [26]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="32">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley left Matthew at Richard's cottage and went to[0]see Ryan. He told her that Crusoe Resort's collapse[1]five years ago came after their blindly aggressive[2]development damaged the local environment. He also[3]said that Sayoko visited Lake Juliet 13 years ago[4]because she was torn between her responsibilities as a[5]mother and her dreams of continuing her scientific[6]research. Ryan also gave Ashley a kaleidoscope that[7]Sayoko had given him many years ago. Inside it was[8]a beautiful cherry blossom pattern.[9] [10]On the way back to see Matthew, Ashley ran into a [11]friend from high school, Janet. She was at Lake Juliet[12]for the last weekend of her summer holiday to visit her[13]cousin - Elizabeth. The girls chatted and then went their[14]separate ways. But as soon as Ashley got back, Janet[15]phoned to ask her to come over to Elizabeth's[16]house so they could talk.[17] [18]Matthew asked Ashley to take the music player,[19]handkerchief and ID card he had found and give them[20]back to Elizabeth. Ashley decided to go on her own[21]to return them.[22]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="33">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="34">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="35">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="36">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="37">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="38">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="39">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="40">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After a call from Janet saying she needed some advice,[0]Ashley left Matthew at the cottage and went to[1]Elizabeth's house. Janet asked Ashley how she could [2]help Elizabeth to get along better with her father, Rex.[3]As they were talking, Rex arrived back from the lab and[4]Ashley learned that he was an old friend of both of her[5]parents.[6] [7]Elizabeth, convinced Rex was hiding things from her,[8]searched his room and found letters addressed to her[9]from her mother. She broke down crying. Ashley [10]left the music player, handkerchief and ID card that[11]Matthew had given her and went back to her father's[12]cottage.[13] [14]When she returned, Matthew had vanished again but had[15]left a note saying he had gone looking for his father.[16]Ashley used Princess' sense of smell to find him at the[17]clock tower. Matthew said that he came to the clock[18]tower because he remembered his mother crying there.[19] [20]His mother had told him that the crest on the clock[21]tower door was the family crest of the man who built[22]the tower. As they were talking, the sky suddenly got[23]cloudy. They ran back to the cottage, but it started to[24]rain before they could get to the covered bridge. They[25]sheltered there until the rain stopped, and when the sky[26]cleared, they saw a beautiful rainbow.[27] [28]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="41">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When they got back to the cottage, Matthew collapsed[0]with a fever. Ashley put him to bed and went to look [1]for some medicine, but found nothing. Matthew refused[2]to see a doctor, so Ashley went to Bob to get some ice[3]as there wasn't enough in the freezer. Bob's ice machine[4]was broken, but he did tell Ashley about an old lady[5]who could give her good fever medicine.[6] [7]Ashley got the medicine recipe and red herbs from[8]Charlotte, who also lent her a mortar and pestle. Ashley[9]found some pure water and boiled the herbs to make[10]the medicine, then gave it to Matthew. They talked about[11]how she got the recipe, and Matthew remembered that[12]he had been to Charlotte's house before with his father.[13] [14]Matthew was still too ill to go out, so Ashley left him to[15]rest while she went to ask Charlotte about the clock[16]tower and see if she knew anything about Michael[17]Crusoe.[18] [19]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="42">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>On the way to Charlotte's house, Ashley met Lucy,[0]Charlotte's niece. She had just been sent away by her[1]aunt and was fuming at how stubborn Charlotte could[2]be. Before leaving, Lucy told Ashley about the clock[3]tower and Charlotte's daughter, Olivia, who eloped five[4]years ago.[5] [6]Ashley returned Charlotte's mortar and pestle and [7]thanked her for the medicine. She told Charlotte about[8]Matthew's search for his father and asked her if she [9]could look in the clock tower. Her determination [10]impressed Charlotte, who told Ashley  about her[11]daughter Olivia and the three keys to the clock tower.[12]If Ashley could find those keys, she could search the [13]tower. [14] [15]After retrieving two of the keys from Charlotte's shed,[16]Ashley found a letter from Olivia with one of the keys[17]and read it aloud to Charlotte, who then talked a little[18]about her feelings for her daughter. Charlotte realised[19]she wanted to hear the clock tower bell again, and[20]entrusted Ashley with making it ring once more.[21]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="43">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="44">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="45">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="46">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="47">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="48">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="49">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 5 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="50">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Charlotte did not know how to restart the clock in the[0]tower, but she was sure that her father would have left[1]something there as a clue. Matthew had recovered from[2]his fever, and he went with Ashley to the clock tower.[3]They unlocked the door, went in, fixed the broken[4]stairs and went up to the main clock room. Matthew [5]admitted that he was afraid of heights and stayed[6]huddled in a corner of the room. [7] [8]With help from the clues in the tower, Ashley used the[9]keys to get the clock started. Matthew got up to look at[10]the machinery and saw that there was a puzzle box[11]inside it, identical to one he had seen before at his[12]father's office. Afterwards, they decided to go to the[13]old Crusoe Resort offices together. [14] [15]As they left the clock tower, the bell rang and, as she[16]heard it, Ashley had a recollection of her mother[17]receiving her tear-shaped pendant from someone.[18] [19]They met Elizabeth at the covered bridge and found out[20]that Princess was her beloved pet. Elizabeth also[21]apologised for accusing Matthew of stealing her music[22]player. Ashley insisted on visiting Charlotte to return[23]the keys before going to the old Crusoe Resort offices.[24] [25]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="51">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley went to thank Charlotte and return the clock [0]tower keys. Charlotte explained about the time Michael[1]Crusoe came to apologise to her after employees from[2]his company damaged her property. He had Matthew[3]with him, who was suffering from a fever. Charlotte[4]told them that the pollution was not Michael's fault,[5]and that someone appeared to have fallen from the [6]tower five years ago, but a body was never found.[7] [8]Ashley told Charlotte that she had learned a lot about[9]her mother since arriving at Lake Juliet and showed her[10]the kaleidoscope. Charlotte told Ashley that it was a [11]chamber kaleidoscope and gave Ashley her butterfly [12]chamber.[13]She also showed Ashley the blanket that brought her as[14]much happiness as the kaleidoscope brought Ashley,[15]and Ashley realised that she had seen it before.[16] [17]Charlotte informed them about a short cut to the old[18]Crusoe Resort offices and told Ashley to look after[19]Matthew and to send him back to her house if things[20]became too difficult.[21] [22]When they arrived at the old offices, the gate was tied[23]up with rope. Ashley noticed a tunnel that came out[24]inside the fence and used the Connect function on the [25]DAS to find a saw, which they used to open the gate[26]and enter the building.[27]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="52">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After deactivating the card lock, Ashley and Matthew[0]went inside the old Crusoe Resort offices. The corridor[1]and stairs were obstructed by boxes, so they couldn't[2]go upstairs. They used a key found in the office to get[3]into the reference room, where Matthew remembered[4]hiding his sister Kelly's doll. [5]Ashley looked in the lockers and found the doll under[6]a shelf. As she handed it to Matthew, he said that Kelly[7]was there. Ashley turned around and saw a little girl.[8]As soon as Matthew handed her the doll, she smiled and[9]faded away.[10] [11]Matthew tried to chase after her, but Ashley stopped[12]him. He then remembered how Kelly died after falling into[13]the lake. Ashley told him that Kelly's death wasn't his[14]fault and told him about her first best friend, who she[15]would never see again.[16] [17]When they came out into the corridor, the man with the [18]sunglasses, John Smith, was there. He gave his real [19]name as Greg Davis and said that Michael Crusoe had[20]been giving him material for a story. He told them that[21]he had arranged to meet Michael five years ago to get[22]a puzzle box which contained his report on the pollution[23]of Lake Juliet, but Michael never arrived. Greg then gave[24]Ashley the code to open the puzzle box.[25]Ashley told Matthew to open the box, but he was afraid[26]of remembering anything more and ran away.[27] [28]She found him on the way to Capulet Point and [29]convinced him to be strong. They opened the puzzle[30]box and found inside a report proving that JC Valley[31]had polluted Lake Juliet. Ashley entrusted Greg with[32]making the report public. [33] [34]A message then arrived from Richard, asking Ashley[35]to come to JC Valley urgently. Ashley headed there[36]with Matthew in tow.[37]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="53">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="54">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="55">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="56">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="57">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="58">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="59">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 6 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="60">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley was met at the front door of JC Valley by Gina, [0]who refused to allow Matthew in. Not happy with leaving[1]him by himself, Ashley told Matthew to wait for her at[2]Charlotte's house and followed Gina into the lab.[3]After showing Ashley to the meeting room, Gina [4]denied that there were any system problems and said[5]she never called Richard. She left, telling Ashley to wait.[6]Then a message arrived on the DAS from Richard -[7]"Something's happened at the lab. Please take the TAS[8]and go home right away."[9] [10]Confused by Gina's denials and Richard's message,[11]Ashley found a new battery for the TAS and unlocked[12]the door so she could get to Richard's office. Ashley[13]entered the reception and noticed another room [14]behind it, where Richard could be seen on a screen.[15]Ashley managed to open the door and get in, then[16]used the Video Conferencing system to call her [17]father.[18]Richard changed which cameras could be seen using[19]the Connect function on the DAS, but just as he told[20]her to wait there for him, he was cut off. Using Connect,[21]Ashley could see him unconscious on his office floor.[22] [23]Panicked, Ashley looked at the control panel of the VC[24]system and found Greg Davis' informant, Mike Tyler. She[25]called him and told him what had happened, and Mike[26]came to the security room. After hearing Ashley's story,[27]Mike told her to go to his office and wait there.[28] [29]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="61">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After checking on the security system, Mike returned to[0]the office he shared with Gina, where Ashley was.[1]Ashley saw Gina's name tag and told Mike that it wasn't[2]the person she had met earlier. Mike told Ashley to wait[3]in his office while he went to check on Richard.[4] [5]After Mike left, a call came on the VC system. It came[6]from Sofia's room, but the woman on the screen called[7]herself Gina. While a confused Ashley spoke to her[8]to try to determine what was real, the woman she[9]had thought to be Gina came into the room, but quickly[10]left again. The real Gina, on the screen, told Ashley[11]that the woman she had just seen was Sofia. [12]Ashley told Gina what had happened to Richard, and [13]they decided to meet in his office. [14] [15]As Ashley made her way to Richard's office, she saw[16]Sofia running away from her down the corridor and [17]realised that it was Sofia who had stolen her bag. When[18]Ashley arrived at her father's office, she found Mike[19]collapsed on the floor. She tried to wake him, but he[20]muttered something about an e-mail before falling[21]unconscious again. She looked at her father's computer[22]and found a half-written e-mail - "I've finally found out[23]who it is. It's Sofia. Hurry..."[24] [25]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="62">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley was stopped by a closed security shutter on her[0]way to Sofia's room, but she noticed a gap underneath[1]it and remembered that there was a card lock on the[2]other side. Using the TAS and a mirror, she unlocked the[3]shutter and got into Sofia's room, where she found Gina[4]collapsed on the floor. Sofia arrived and locked them[5]both in the room, saying she wouldn't let them interfere[6]with what she was doing. Ashley woke Gina and told her[7]that Mike had also been attacked.[8] [9]Gina printed out an e-mail which proved that Sofia had[10]leaked information, and then Ashley used the VC system[11]in Richard's room to call for help. Mike answered and,[12]although he was unable to hear them, Ashley managed[13]to communicate through gestures that the door would[14]not open. Mike told them how to use the emergency[15]door release and they escaped. They met Mike in the[16]corridor, who told them to wait in the office. [17] [18]Ashley went back to Gina's office with her and used her[19]scanner pen to decrypt Sofia's e-mail as Gina's arm [20]was injured. It said: "Judd's documents are no longer[21]necessary. Your last task is to find information relating[22]to mnemonic fluid."[23]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="63">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="64">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="65">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="66">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="67">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="68">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="69">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 7 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="70">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While Ashley was talking to Gina about Sofia, Ryan[0]called on the VC. Gina and Ashley told him about[1]Richard and Sofia, and Ryan said to come to his office.[2] [3]When Ryan opened the security gate for them, Gina[4]told him that her and Richard's investigation had shown[5]that Sofia was leaking information. She handed over [6]the e-mail she had as evidence, then went back to her [7]room to check the entry and exit records for the lab.[8]Ashley went with Ryan to his office, where he asked her[9]why she was at JC Valley. She told him about the fake[10]DAS message.[11] [12]Ryan theorised that Richard had called Ashley to Lake[13]Juliet to force her latent memories to surface. He told[14]her that Richard was safe and he had just seen him.[15]Ryan was about to go and get Richard when Rex called[16]on the VC. Ryan went to report what had happened to[17]Richard and about Sofia to Rex before finding Richard.[18] [19]After Ryan left, there was another call on the VC - from[20]Richard. He was shocked to see Ashley there, and told[21]her not to give the TAS to anyone, not to trust Ryan[22]and to go and meet Rex - then the call was cut off.[23] [24]Confused, Ashley did as her father said and unlocked[25]the door to go and find Rex.[26] [27]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="71">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley went into Rex's office to find Sofia there. When[0]she asked about Richard, Sofia replied that she had no[1]idea where Richard was.[2]Sofia told Ashley that her goal was to get information[3]on the EC Project, and that her only remaining task[4]was to find the prototype mnemonic fluid.[5]When Ashley told Sofia that they had given the[6]evidence mail to Ryan, Sofia laughed and revealed that[7]Ryan was her partner. Sofia said that if Ashley let her[8]leave, she would not harm her. She then offered to tell[9]Ashley everything she knew.[10]Ashley promised that she wouldn't leave the room[11]until she found the secret compartment in it.[12] [13]After Sofia left, Ashley looked through Judd's biography[14]and used a celestial globe to open the compartment.[15]Inside was an empty case with "1994 S - R" written[16]inside it. [17] [18]Then, Rex arrived. Ashley told him that Richard was[19]attacked and that Sofia had been leaking information.[20]Rex in turn told her the story behind the pendant he[21]gave to Sayoko 13 years ago.[22]It contained her most important memory.[23] [24]The two heard a voice from the VC. It was Ryan, saying[25]"Beginning Another experiment".[26]Rex told him to stop the experiment, but Ryan closed[27]the call. Ashley and Rex rushed to the Another lab.[28] [29]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="72">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When Ashley and Rex arrived in the Another lab,[0]Richard was lying unconsious inside the memory control[1]unit while Ryan stood in the control room. Rex ordered[2]him to stop the experiment, but Ryan refused. Ryan[3]told them that he had found out about Richard's search[4]for the truth behind Sayoko's death and that Richard[5]had taken some of her research materials. Ryan then[6]prepared an experiment to erase parts of Richard's[7]memory. Ashley pleaded with Ryan not to erase her[8]father's memories, but he refused to stop unless she[9]found a box that had belonged to her mother in[10]Richard's office and returned with the contents.[11]Ashley found a rectangular box in Richard's office with[12]an upgrade module for the TAS inside. After connecting[13]it to the TAS, she heard her mother's voice. Sayoko's[14]recording said that she had created the TAS as a final[15]security measure to prevent Another being used for the[16]wrong reasons. [17] [18]When Ashley returned to the Another lab, Richard was[19]just emerging from the memory control unit.[20]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="73">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 4[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="74">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 5[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="75">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 6[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="76">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 7[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="77">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 8[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="78">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 9[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="79">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 8 Summary 10[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="80">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When Richard emerged from Another, 17 years of his[0]memories had been erased. He even failed to recognise[1]Ashley, his own daughter.[2] [3]Ashley gave Ryan the TAS upgrade module, but what[4]he really wanted was the device that would unlock the[5]security restriction placed on Another. Ashley demanded[6]that Ryan restore her father's memories and he told her[7]that he would consider it if she participated in a memory[8]overwrite experiment. This experiment would remove[9]memories that Ashley wanted to forget and replace[10]them with Sayoko's memories.[11] [12]The experiment was a failure and Ryan refused to[13]restore Richard's memories. Ashley said she would do it[14]herself and produced the TAS. Ryan attempted to take[15]it from her at gunpoint, but Rex attacked him. During[16]the struggle, Ryan's gun went off, injuring Rex. Ryan[17]then fled the room.[18] [19]Following Rex's instructions, Ashley used the TAS to[20]restore Richard's memories. She remembered having[21]seen the laptop containing Judd's documents 13 [22]years ago and unlocked it. It contained a report[23]exposing all of his secrets about Sayoko, Another and[24]Ryan, who was actually his son.[25] [26]Richard and Ashley called Gina and left Rex in her care.[27]They then went after Ryan.[28] [29]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="81">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ashley and Richard raced through the underground[0]tunnel to find Ryan.[1] [2]As they went, Richard told Ashley how he used[3]to go to the spring outside the cave with Sayoko[4]a long time ago. On their way out of the cave[5]after unblocking the exit, they came across the[6]Secret Spring. After seeing the pure, clear water, Richard[7]and Ashley vowed to help restore Lake Juliet.[8] [9]When they reached the lake, they saw Ryan taking a[10]boat towards a small island. Boarding an old boat,[11]Richard and Ashley continued to follow him. [12] [13]During the lull of the boat trip, Richard told Ashley that[14]he had come to JC Valley in the hopes of tracking down[15]the person who was truly behind Sayoko's death and[16]that he was close to discovering the truth. They [17]disembarked onto the small island.[18]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="82">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="83">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="84">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="85">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="86">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="87">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="88">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="89">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
</Session>