<Session title="LOAD_HISTORY.BMG">
  <Sentence id="0">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got a parcel out of the blue from my dad, who works[0]at JC Valley. It had an invitation for a family camp that[1]weekend and a new model of his DAS handheld thing.[2]Jessica guilt-tripped me into going, so I had to[3]cancel my own plans for the weekend and get on the[4]bus to Lake Juliet...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我收到了一份爸爸寄给我的蓝色包裹。[0]他现在在JC山谷工作。包裹里面有一份[1]周末家庭露营招待券和他最新制造的手[2]持设备DAS。杰西卡说服了我让我去，[3]于是我取消了我周末所有的计划，搭上[4]了开往朱丽叶湖的大巴……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="1">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As soon I got off the bus, someone stole my bag! And [0]Dad wasn't there, even though he'd promised Jessica[1]he'd come and pick me up.[2]I was trying to decide what to do when a message from[3]Dad arrived on the DAS: "Go ahead and check in at[4]the guesthouse." [5]Okay, let's find this guesthouse...[6]</Original>
    <Translation>我刚一下车，我的包就被偷了！爸爸[0]本来答应杰西卡会来接我的，但他却[1]没出现……[2]我还在想该如何是好时，爸爸发来的[3]一条信息出现在DAS的屏幕上：“快[4]去接待处登记吧。” [5]好吧，让我找找接待处在哪儿……[6]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="2">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I got the message to "go ahead and check in at[0]the guesthouse" from Dad, I went there but the door[1]was locked. So, how am I supposed to check in? [2] [3]I'll have a look around and see if there's someone [4]nearby who can help me...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我收到爸爸那条“快去接待处登记吧。”的[0]信息之后，就去了接待处，但是那儿大门紧[1]锁。这下好了，让我怎么登记啊？ [2] [3]我得四处看看，说不定附近有人可以帮上忙 [4]呢……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="3">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While I was looking for the guesthouse staff, I met[0]Dan, a Forest Ranger. He promised to look for my bag[1]for me, and told me about the villa that had burned[2]down three days ago and about some problem people[3]in the area. [4]Okay, time to check the guesthouse again...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>就在我四处寻找接待处的工作人员时，我遇见[0]了丹，一名护林员。他答应我，会替我留意下[1]我的包的。他还告诉我了三天前别墅发生了火[2]灾被烧毁的事情，以及这附近最近老是出现[3]些不三不四的人。 [4]好吧，再去接待处看看吧……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="4">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dan told me that the holiday staff at the guesthouse[0]are always taking breaks, but never for too long. When[1]I checked there again, the door was open![2]There's a shop inside with souvenirs and stuff. [3] [4]I just want to get this check-in over with...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>丹和我说，接待处的工作人员老是给自己[0]放假，但是只是开一会儿的小差。当我再[1]去的时候，惊喜地发现门竟然是开着的！[2]接待处里面是个卖纪念品和其他东西的商店。 [3] [4]我其实只是想办理登记手续啊……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="5">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got to the guesthouse to check in and the door was[0]finally open, but no one was there. Then Tommy, who's[1]working there, appeared from the back room.[2]I checked in, got my ID card and filled in a missing items[3]police report for my stolen bag. Tommy told me some[4]strange things have happened around here recently...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我又去了次接待处，门终于开了。[0]但是里面没人。然后这儿的工作人[1]员汤米从后面的房间里现身了。[2]我登了记，拿到了我的ID卡，还填[3]完了失物招领单。汤米告诉我了一[4]些最近在这儿发生的奇怪的事情……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="6">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Tommy, who's working at the campsite for the summer,[0]got me checked in, gave me an ID card and filed my[1]police report. He told me about the mysterious lone[2]camper, the fire at the villa and food going missing[3]from the store room. He also told me that I can[4]buy things at the shop with my ID card![5]</Original>
    <Translation>汤米只是这个夏天在这儿上班，他帮我办[0]完了登记手续，给我张ID卡，还帮我填完[1]了失物招领单。他告诉我，除了我和爸爸[2]还有个神秘的旅客，还说了别墅大火的事[3]情，另外，食物也从储藏室里神秘失踪。[4]他还告诉我凭ID卡也能在商店购物耶！[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="7">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I was about to head out to find Dad's campsite when I[0]realised I didn't know where it was. As I asked Tommy[1]for directions, the phone rang. It was a girl he knew. [2]He gave me directions to Dad's campsite when he got[3]off the phone. [4]I guess I'd better head on over there...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>正打算向爸爸的营地进发的时候忽然想起来，[0]我还不知道它在哪儿呢！就在我向汤米询问营[1]地方位的时候，电话响了。是个他认识的女孩 [2]子。挂了电话之后他终于告诉了我爸爸营地的[3]具体方位。[4]我想我最好马上就过去……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="8">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As I unlocked the campsite gate using my ID card, I [0]suddenly had a flashback about my mom. Why am I[1]having flashbacks here of all places? I don't understand[2]it, but I clearly remember her standing at these gates...[3] [4]Dad's waiting at the campsite, I should go...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>就在我用自己的ID卡打开了营地大门的时候，[0]眼前忽然出现了关于妈妈的闪影。为什么我会[1]在这个地方出现关于妈妈的闪影呢？我不明白。[2]但是我能清楚地记得她就站在这个门前面……[3] [4]爸爸还在营地等我呢，我该走了……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="9">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I got through the gate on the way to Dad's [0]campsite, I passed a guy and a girl talking about [1]something she'd lost. They passed me by like I wasn't [2]even there and went on through the gate. [3] [4]I'm nearly at Dad's campsite now...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>当我通过前往爸爸营地的大门时，从我身边[0]走过了一男一女，他们在说什么那个女孩丢[1]了东西。他们从我身边走过的时候好像完全[2]没注意到我这个大活人一样。 [3] [4]就快到爸爸的营地了……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="10">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After going through the campsite gate, I passed by a [0]guy and a girl and arrived at Dad's campsite. He hadn't[1]changed a bit - he didn't even notice I don't have my[2]favourite bag with me, and all he was worried about[3]was his precious DAS! I don't even know how to talk to[4]him any more...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>穿过营地大门之后，我遇见了一对男女， [0]之后来到了爸爸的营地。他一点都没变。[1]他甚至都没注意到我没拿着我最喜欢的包。[2]而他关心的只有他那无比珍贵的DAS！我[3]都不知道该如何和他交流了……[4][5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="11">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I finally found Dad's campsite. He was waiting for me [0]there, but after not seeing him for six months we didn't[1]start off very well... Whenever I talk to him, the only [2]thing I want to do is complain...[3]While Dad got the barbecue ready, I took my empty can[4]to the recycling machine and got a token...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我终于来到了爸爸的营地。他已经在那里[0]等我了，但是这半年后的重逢刚开始并不[1]怎么顺利……无论什么时候我和他说话，[2]我想做的只有冲他抱怨……[3]就在爸爸准备烧烤的时候，我拿着喝完的[4]空饮料罐来到回收机前，换到了一枚硬币……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="12">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dad forgot the most important thing for a barbecue - [0]the charcoal! I was so mad, I told him that I didn't even[1]want to be here. After that, Dad told me that Mom had [2]brought me here to Lake Juliet 13 years ago. He also[3]gave me the TAS, a machine that Mom developed.[4]Okay, Dad, I'll go get the charcoal for you...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>爸爸忘记了对于烧烤来说最重要的事——木炭！[0]我气极了，叫喊着我根本不想来这儿。然后爸爸[1]告诉我，13年前妈妈曾带我来过朱丽叶湖。他还[2]给了我一个叫TAS的东西，是妈妈发明的一种仪[3]器。[4]好吧，爸爸，我这就去帮你拿木炭……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="13">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The guesthouse was empty when I went there for [0]charcoal, but I heard a noise coming from the back[1]room. I looked through the blinds and saw a huge dog[2]and some kid with a teddy bear... [3] [4]Hey! That's my teddy bear![5]</Original>
    <Translation>我去拿木炭的时候接待处空无一人。 [0]但是我听到从后面的房间里传来了奇[1]怪的声音。我透过百叶窗一看，看到[2]了一只大狗和一个抱着泰迪熊的小孩……[3] [4]天呐！那是我的泰迪熊！[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="14">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The guesthouse was empty, but I heard some noises.[0]I looked through the blind to the store room and saw a[1]huge dog and a kid carrying my teddy bear! I used the[2]TAS to unlock the door, but they'd already gone.[3] [4]I've got to find them![5]</Original>
    <Translation>接待处里没人，但是我却听到了奇怪的声音。[0]我透过百叶窗看见在储藏室里有只大狗和一个[1]小孩，那小鬼拿着我的泰迪熊！我用TAS解开[2]了门锁，但是他们却不见了踪影。[3] [4]我一定要找到他们！[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="15">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to the guesthouse to get charcoal, but heard[0]noises from the back of the shop. I used the TAS to[1]get into the store room, and found a huge dog and a[2]kid carrying a teddy bear...my teddy bear![3] [4]I've got to find them![5]</Original>
    <Translation>我去接待处取木炭，却听到从商店后面[0]房间里传来奇怪的声音。我用TAS进入[1]储藏室，却发现了一条大狗和一个抱着[2]泰迪熊的小孩……我的泰迪熊！[3] [4]我一定得找到他们！[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="16">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I followed the kid I saw in the store room out the back[0]of the guesthouse to a wire fence. I tried to get through[1]the same hole he'd used, but that massive dog just sat[2]right in front of it![3] [4]I've got to get rid of this dog and find that kid![5]</Original>
    <Translation>我跟着在储藏室看见的小孩来到了[0]接待处后面的护栏网处。我想学着[1]他的样子从洞里钻过去，但是那条[2]体型庞大的狗挡住了我！[3] [4]我得想办法摆脱这条狗，去追那个小鬼！[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="17">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I finally got that big dog to move away from the[0]hole in the fence so I could get through and chase the[1]kid. But then Tommy showed up and accused me of [2]breaking into and stealing from the locked store room![3] [4]How can I prove it wasn't me?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我终于把那条大狗从护栏网的洞[0]前面弄开了，这下好去追那个小[1]孩了。但是汤米偏偏这时出现，[2]还指责我闯入储藏室偷东西！[3] [4]我怎么样才能证明那不是我呢？[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="18">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Tommy accepted it wasn't me messing up the stores and[0]he gave me the charcoal. Before I went back to Dad's[1]campsite, Tommy told me about the thefts and the fire[2]at the villa. He showed me a picture of it from before[3]the fire...and I had another flashback about my mom![4]I've got to get back to the campsite, Dad's waiting...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>汤米终于明白了在储藏室捣蛋的不是我，[0]然后给了我木炭。就在我打算回营地的时[1]候，汤米告诉我了些关于最近的偷盗和别[2]墅火灾的事。他给我看了一张别墅在失火[3]前拍的照片……而妈妈的闪影再次出现了！[4]我得赶回营地去，爸爸在等我呢……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="19">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I was nearly back at the campsite with the charcoal[0]when I ran into Dad hurrying the other way. He'd been [1]called back to the lab for some emergency. He said that[2]someone called Gina from the lab would come and have [3]the barbecue with me.[4]Great. Now I have to wait for Gina, whoever she is...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我拿着木炭急冲冲地往营地跑，遇见[0]了刚从营地出来的爸爸。因为实验室[1]的突发状况所以他得马上赶回去。他[2]说，实验室的吉娜接了电话，说马上[3]就会过来陪我烧烤的。[4]好吧。现在我就老老实实等吉娜吧，天知道她是谁……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="20">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I came to Lake Juliet, near the JC Valley labs where my[0]dad works, to meet him for a camping trip. It started[1]badly with my bag being stolen, but I found out from [2]Dad that Mom brought me here 13 years ago. [3]Maybe that's why these memories of her have started[4]coming back now...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>我来到了朱丽叶湖，为的是和我的爸爸一起进行[0]一次野营旅行。他就在湖边的JC山谷实验室工作。[1]虽然一开始就不顺利——我的包被偷了，但是我[2]从爸爸那里得知，妈妈13年前和我一起来过这儿。 [3]也许这就是为什么，关于她的记忆开始不断地涌[4]现出来……[5]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="21">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="22">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="23">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="24">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="25">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="26">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="27">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="28">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="29">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>[0]</Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="30">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina never turned up at the campsite - instead I met[0]Ryan, one of Dad's co-workers. I was sure I'd seen him[1]before...but he told me that childhood memories are[2]vague and unreliable. Then he asked me about why I'd[3]come to Lake Juliet - and it turns out he knew my mom![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="31">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ryan said we should start preparing the barbecue, so I[0]got the charcoal burning. The food was great, and I[1]even ate the peppers, which I normally hate. Ryan [2]talked to me about Mom, and unlike Dad, he really[3]listened to me, too. I'd really love to talk to him more[4]about Mom...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="32">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After the barbecue, Ryan told me about how he'd met[0]Mom, and I told him about my bag being stolen. [1] [2]We were enjoying talking, just the two of us, when this [3]girl Elizabeth turned up and demanded that Ryan come[4]and help her look for her music player...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="33">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>This girl, Elizabeth, daughter of the head of JC Valley,[0]turned up at the campsite and dragged Ryan off to help[1]her look for her music player.[2]Alone again, I got another message from Dad: "I can't [3]make it back to the campsite, can you bring my bag to[4]the cottage?" Fine, I'll bring your stupid bag...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="34">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After Ryan and Elizabeth left, I got another message[0]from Dad on the DAS: "Bring my bag and meet me at[1]the cottage." When I picked up Dad's backpack, I also[2]found Ryan's briefcase. I'd better go and give it to him[3]before I try to find Dad...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="35">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I met Ranger Dan again as I left the campsite to go[0]to Dad's cottage. When he heard I was Dr Robins' [1]daughter, he started talking about how he met Dad. [2]He also showed me a picture of the boy who had run[3]away from home - the kid from the guesthouse store[4]room! Hey, there's someone in the other campsite...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="36">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I finished talking to Dan and headed towards the[0]lake, I saw Ryan and Elizabeth at the other campsite.[1]I gave Ryan back his briefcase, and he asked if I had[2]remembered anything else. I told him that Dad wasn't [3]coming back to the campsite and I was going to his [4]cottage instead. Okay, off to Dad's...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="37">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I came out onto the lake shore and got a good look at[0]Lake Juliet - and had another sudden flashback about[1]Mom. Then I saw the runaway kid, Matthew Crusoe.[2]When I tried to talk to him, he ran away. I chased after[3]him, but that ginormous hairy dog got in the way. Again.[4]Where did he go?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="38">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I came across this shack while trying to find Matthew.[0]There was a huge wooden board blocking the entrance.[1]But I just had to talk to Matthew about that teddy bear[2]he was holding, so I moved the board aside and went[3]inside to look for him.[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="39">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The shack was deserted. I heard a noise and headed[0]outside and found a well - with my teddy bear beside it![1]Yes! I found him![2]Suddenly, I heard something from the well - "Help me!"[3]I opened the cover on the well to find Matthew inside.[4]I need to ask him about my bag...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="40">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I rescued him from the well, Matthew told me that[0]he'd found my teddy bear at the villa ruins - and my[1]bag had been there too. When I asked him why he'd run[2]away from home, he said something about trying to find[3]his kidnapped father, but I'm not sure if he was telling[4]the truth. I want to see where he found my bag...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="41">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As I headed out to where Matthew said he'd seen my[0]bag, I saw that massive dog from the lake shore again,[1]sitting beside a stack of crates in the shack. I could just[2]see a pink music player behind them... The crates were[3]too heavy for me to lift alone, so I couldn't get it out.[4]Wonder whose it is?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="42">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I didn't find my bag at the villa ruins, but my band[0]scores were there. When I saw the door knocker under[1]them, I had another flashback about Mom. Then[2]Matthew arrived, and I ended up telling him about how[3]she died... Another message from Dad arrived: "I'm [4]back at the cottage now. I'm waiting for you here, so[5]hurry."[6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="43">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I left the villa ruins to go to Dad's cottage, and met[0]Tommy and Sam along the way. They're in a band with[1]Elizabeth, and I found out they're entering the band[2]contest I want to compete in![3] [4]I have got to find Dad's cottage...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="44">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I had another flashback - this time when I saw the clock[0]tower across the lake. I know I've seen Mom standing in[1]front of it! I met Matthew again at the boathouse. He[2]was trying to get in to look for clues about his dad. I [3]can't let him go in there on his own, so I guess I'd[4]better go with him.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="45">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I distracted Matthew so that I could use the TAS to[0]unlock the boathouse door and get us inside without[1]him seeing it. There was no one there, so we went out[2]through an open door to the pier. While looking for[3]clues about his dad, we found a bag floating on[4]the lake... Is it mine?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="46">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Matt helped me look in the boathouse for something[0]we could use to haul in the bag from the lake. While we[1]were looking, he showed me a photo of him with his dad,[2]mom and little sister - and he remembered going boating[3]with his dad here on the lake. [4]I need to try and remember more about Mom...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="47">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got the bag out of the lake! But it wasn't mine. When[0]Matt saw it, he realised that it was the same bag[1]as the one in his family photo. We wanted to look[2]inside, but the case had a combination lock.[3]Four letters...what could they be?[4]Maybe Matt has an idea...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="48">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dan turned up at the boathouse pier! Matt heard[0]him coming and hid behind the door until he could get[1]away without Dan seeing him. I told Dan about the bag[2]from the lake, and he told me more about Matt running[3]away from home last year. I've got to keep him from[4]finding Matt for just a little longer...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="49">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dad's co-worker, Ryan, turned up to keep me company[0]at the campsite, and told me about how he'd met Mom.[1]I met the runaway kid, Matt, on the way to Dad's[2]cottage. We searched the boathouse together and pulled[3]his dad's bag in from the lake. Then Dan turned up, [4]and Matt ran away again...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="50">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="51">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="52">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="53">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="54">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="55">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="56">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="57">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="58">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="59">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="60">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I handed Matt's dad's bag over to Dan at the[0]boathouse, I went looking for Matt. Dan said he [1]found him at the old cottage last year. [2] [3]He wouldn't be hiding in the same place again... [4]Would he?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="61">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While wandering around looking for Matt, I found[0]this old cottage - it's got to be where Dan said he[1]found Matt last year. The door wasn't locked so I[2]went in...[3]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="62">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I found a secret cellar in the old cottage! And [0]Matt was down there. He absolutely refuses to go [1]home... After listening to his reasons, I promised to[2]spend the day helping to look for clues about his dad,[3]as long as he promised to go home if we don't find [4]anything. [5]Right, let's get searching for clues![6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="63">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Matt showed me a map for some treasure he buried[0]last year. I used the electric hotplate to make the ink [1]appear, but it tripped the circuit breaker. I managed[2]to get the power back on and found a really old photo[3]of Mom and Dad. When I showed it to Matt, he said[4]he'd seen Dad near the lake. [5]Let's get to Dad's cottage![6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="64">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got another message from Dad on the DAS: "I'll come[0]and meet you at the covered bridge, so wait for me [1]there". So, we set off to find the covered bridge.[2] [3]You'll meet my dad soon, Matt![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="65">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We ran into Elizabeth on the way to the covered bridge.[0]She accused Matt of stealing her music player! And[1]to make things worse, Dad overheard her and was on[2]her side too! I was so mad I started yelling at him...[3]So Matt took off yet again.[4]Dad apologised and I headed off to find Matt...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="66">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I found Matt at the Lonely Oak, and he told me a[0]bit about his memories of his dad and his sister Kelly.[1]I used his map to find his treasure, his last letter from [2]his mom. After talking about his mom and dad, we [3]decided to find Elizabeth's music player and that [4]handkerchief to prove his innocence![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="67">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Matt told me that when he found the music player,[0]it was wrapped in a handkerchief. We went to the old[1]mine entrance where he'd found the player and got the [2]handkerchief. We also found that colossal dog, whose[3]name seems to be "Princess". Now we need to get to[4]the shack and get that music player...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="68">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After talking at the Lonely Oak, I went with Matt[0]to the shack to find the music player. I lifted up the [1]crate while he pulled it out from behind them. Now we[2]need to go to the old mines where he'd found it first to[3]get the handkerchief it was wrapped in...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="69">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After talking at the Lonely Oak, I went with Matt to[0]the old mines to get the handkerchief, and to the shack[1]to get Elizabeth's music player, to prove his innocence -[2]she's GOING to apologise to him! The handkerchief is[3]the same brand as her bandanna, just like he said. [4]For now, let's head to Dad's cottage...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="70">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I saw Mr Sunglasses heading for the clock tower! [0]Matt didn't want to go, so I told him to wait for me[1]in the cabin. I caught up with the guy by the mermaid[2]statue. He said his name is John Smith and he's[3]investigating something that happened five years ago... [4]And I have to stay away from the clock tower?![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="71">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Even though Mr Smith told me to stay away, I just had[0]to see the clock tower - and that door with the crest [1]that I remembered turned out to be the clock tower [2]door! When I got to the covered bridge with Matt, [3]the gate was locked. I made him promise not to [4]tell anyone before showing him the TAS and using it to[5]open the gate....[6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="72">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got to the cottage and I gave Dad back the bag I'd[0]been carrying around for him. He really did apologise[1]to Matt. I told Dad about Matt and what I had[2]remembered at the campsite after he left, and he told[3]me that I don't have to force myself to remember[4]about Mom... Thanks, Dad.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="73">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We'd just got talking back at the cottage when the[0]phone rang. It was Gina from the lab, saying there was[1]some problem with the security system. Dad said to [2]wait for him to come back and headed out. I really[3]wanted to keep talking... Matt had a good idea, to[4]use Dad's computer to look for clues. Let's do it![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="74">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We used Dad's computer upstairs to look for clues[0]about Matt's dad. I searched for anything about[1]Michael or his company, but wasn't able to find any[2]clues about Michael. I did find out that his company,[3]Crusoe Resort, really did go bankrupt five years ago.[4]Okay, Matt, let's see what else we can find out...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="75">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Jessica called! She told me that when Dad accepted[0]the job at JC Valley, he'd apparently received a[1]mysterious anonymous e-mail. She also told me [2]she'd sent my guitar ahead to the contest venue like [3]she promised. Dad, I've got loads to talk to you about[4]when you get back![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="76">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Matt pestered me into looking at the folders on Dad's[0]computer. "Water" was full of pictures of...water.[1]While I was checking them out, an e-mail arrived, which[2]reminded me of the anonymous e-mail Jessica told me[3]about. I tried to look at Dad's e-mail, but I need a[4]password... There's got to be a hint somewhere![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="77">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While I was looking at Dad's computer, an e-mail[0]arrived. After Jessica told me about the anonymous[1]e-mail, I had to see it! Dad's e-mail is password[2]protected... But Dad being Dad, he went and left a clue[3]to the password lying around, so I put in the password[4]and got into his e-mail... Sorry, Dad.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="78">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After using Dad's computer to look for clues about[0]Matt's father, I noticed that the DAS has a new[1]function! There's a new option called "Connect" that[2]lets me see feeds from security cameras, and I saw[3]Mr Sunglasses, John Smith, down by the mermaid[4]statue. What is he up to now?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="79">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 20[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="80">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 21[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="81">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 22[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="82">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 23[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="83">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 24[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="84">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 25[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="85">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 26[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="86">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 27[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="87">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 28[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="88">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 29[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="89">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 3 load summary 30[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="90">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After looking up clues about Matt's dad using Dad's[0]computer, I realised my DAS had been upgraded! I can[1]see a new option, "Connect", that wasn't there before.[2]When I checked the new screen, I saw Agent...I mean,[3]Mr Smith near the mermaid statue...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="91">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I took the water testing kit I found in Dad's desk and [0]went out with Matt to the mermaid statue. When we got[1]there, we checked out the new Connect function and [2]looked at the security camera footage. Matt was on[3]it, but I wasn't... Is it something to do with the DAS?[4]Now, I have to test the water...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="92">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I used Dad's water testing kit to check the lake water.[0]After I added the reagent, the lake water reacted by[1]turning red...it's acidic. I told Matt that it looked like the[2]lake was polluted. He asked me what was causing it, [3]but I really haven't a clue.[4]Maybe Dad would know?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="93">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After testing the lake water by the mermaid statue, [0]Matt and I used the photos on Dad's computer to do [1]more water tests in the area. Just as we'd done that,[2]I got a message from Dad on the DAS: "Someone found[3]your stolen bag!"[4]Phew, I'm so relieved...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="94">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I got the message from Dad saying my bag had [0]been found, I headed back to the cottage. But the bag[1]Dan had with him wasn't my bag![2]Dan handed it over to me, so I just kind of took it...[3]What am I going to do? Where's my bag?![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="95">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I got the message from Dad saying my bag had [0]been found, I headed back to the cottage. But...the bag[1]Dan had with him wasn't my bag![2]I told him mine was a bit bigger, and he said he'd found[3]another bag on patrol and would bring it over. [4]Thanks, Dan! I'll wait here for you...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="96">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I got back to the cottage to meet Dan, it turned[0]out the bag he had wasn't mine, but he came back and[1]this time it was the right one![2] [3]I feel kind of bad about putting Dan through so much [4]hassle...but I got my bag back![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="97">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I got back to the cottage, Dan arrived with my[0]bag! I was so happy to have it back. He asked me to [1]check the contents...and my pick case wasn't there![2]I need it for the contest... What am I going to do?[3]I asked Dan where he found it, and he said it was at the[4]half-built cottage... Maybe...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="98">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dan left, and Matt came out from the bathroom where[0]he'd been hiding. I told him about my missing pick case,[1]and also about how I want to be a musician. He said[2]that dreams like that never come true...well, mine will! [3]I'll make it! Matt told me about his dream too...and I[4]heard him whisper to himself that he missed his dad...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="99">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I went to the half-built cottage with Matt, I saw[0]that journalist, Mr Smith, talking to someone on the[1]phone. He noticed we were there after he'd hung up, [2]and he told Matt to hurry up and go home. Then he[3]left...and Matt took off after him![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="100">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I chased after Matt and finally caught up with him in[0]front of a greenhouse. He said he was sure he'd [1]been there before. As we were talking, this old lady [2]appeared and shouted at us for coming into her garden[3]without permission... I apologised to her and went with[4]Matt to look for my pick case.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="101">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I found my pick case! It had fallen down a drain at the[0]half-built cottage. I had the genius idea of filling the [1]drain up with water so it would float to the top, but the[2]hose was ancient and full of holes... I went back to the[3]cottage to see if I could find something to patch it up.[4]Matt was too hungry to go out, so I left him there.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="102">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I fixed the hose and made the pick case float to the top[0]of the drain by filling it with water - go me! I'm so[1]happy, I'd be lost without it. Then, I decided to go to the[2]diner and get something for Matt.[3]When I got there, I could hear someone playing guitar! [4]They're really good. Wonder who it is?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="103">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I went into the diner to see who was playing,[0]it was Tommy and Sam! They told me that the owner let[1]them use the restaurant for practice while he was out[2]making deliveries. I asked where Elizabeth was and it [3]turned out she had to pick up her cousin and would be[4]there later. I want to find out more about their band![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="104">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Bob, who owns the diner, came back and Tommy and[0]Sam left. He knows Dad, and they both really like music![1]He said that even though it's a weekend, everyone is[2]working hard at JC Valley. His diner's specialty is the[3]Salmon Rice Burger, and he also does take away.[4]He's a fun guy to talk to![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="105">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I looked around the diner while Bob made a Salmon Rice[0]Burger for me to take back to Matt. I found a photo of[1]a younger Bob in front of a hamburger stand on the[2]wall - and remembered Mom again! Bob said he created[3]his Salmon Rice Burger from an idea a Japanese woman[4]gave him 13 years ago... It must have been Mom![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="106">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went back to the cottage, and thought Matt had gone[0]again until I heard some noise from upstairs. Matt had[1]a load of Dad's books out on the floor. He really liked[2]the Salmon Rice Burger. We tidied up and I found a[3]magazine with an article on JC Valley. It has a photo of[4]Mr Smith...but the name in the magazine is Greg Davis?![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="107">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The doorbell rang, and it was Ryan! I told him that Dad[0]had gone back to the lab and I was with my friend[1]Matt, but when Ryan heard Matt had something to do [2]with Crusoe Resort, he said I shouldn't hang around[3]with him. He said he'd explain it to me if I came to his[4]cottage. Why is he saying that? I'm going to find out...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="108">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After Ryan left, I invited Matt to go with me to his [0]cottage, but Matt said Ryan sounded really cold so [1]he didn't like him. So he decided to stay. I really need to[2]know why Ryan thinks I shouldn't hang out with Matt.[3]Ryan must have some reason...right?[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="109">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to Ryan's cottage, and he told me why[0]Crusoe Resort went bankrupt five years ago. He also [1]talked about why Mom came here 13 years ago, and[2]how she was torn between being a full-time mom and[3]carrying on as a scientist. And then he said he had [4]something to show me and brought me into his study...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="110">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>There was a kaleidoscope on a table in Ryan's study.[0]I remembered Mom holding an identical one...and[1]Ryan said that this was the same one and she'd given[2]it to him! I looked into it and it had a beautiful cherry[3]blossom image inside. Then the phone rang, and Ryan[4]had to go back to the lab...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="111">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ryan had to go to the lab, so I headed back to the [0]cottage to talk to Matt. On the way, I bumped into[1]Janet, a friend from high school! She was with [2]Elizabeth. Turns out they're cousins and Janet spends[3]the last weekend of every summer holiday here. We[4]talked for a few minutes, then I kept going.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="112">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I ran into Elizabeth and Janet, a friend from high [0]school, on the way back to Dad's cottage. We talked [1]about the summer holidays for a bit, then we went our [2]own ways. Matt asked me about what Ryan had said,[3]and I had just started telling him when the phone rang...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="113">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After making sure that the new Connect function was[0]linked to the security cameras, I used Dad's water[1]testing kit and found that the lake water is polluted.[2]Ryan invited me to his place and told me how Crusoe[3]Resort went bankrupt and about Mom's dilemma. On[4]the way back, I ran into Elizabeth and Janet.[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="114">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 25[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="115">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 26[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="116">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 27[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="117">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 28[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="118">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 29[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="119">
    <Commands>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Chapter 4 load summary 30[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="120">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to the mermaid statue with Matt to check if the[0]DAS Connect function really used the security cameras.[1]Using Dad's water testing kit, I discovered that the lake[2]is polluted... Ryan invited me to his cottage and told me[3]about Crusoe Resort's bankruptcy, and about Mom's [4]worries. On the way back, I met Elizabeth and Janet...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="121">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Janet asked me to come over and give her some advice,[0]so I left Matt at Dad's cottage and went to Elizabeth's[1]place. It's right beside Dad's, but way bigger.[2]I had just arrived when the doorbell rang - it was[3]Tommy. He wanted to talk to Elizabeth about their[4]band...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="122">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Tommy and Elizabeth stayed in the hall while I headed [0]upstairs to Elizabeth's room with Janet. Janet told me[1]that Tommy and Elizabeth were childhood friends and [2]Elizabeth kind of had a crush on him... Okay, so I'm kind[3]of slow to notice these things, I know! Anyway, we [4]said we'd wait for Elizabeth in her room...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="123">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Janet told me that Elizabeth's dad will buy her pretty [0]much anything. But she still doesn't get on with him and[1]that's what she wanted to talk to me about. Apparently[2]Elizabeth hasn't seen her mom since her parents' divorce[3]and it really bothers her. All she has left to remember[4]her mom by is a music box...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="124">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I picked up the music box Elizabeth had on her dresser[0]and opened it to hear it play. It's the only thing she has[1]left to remind her of her mom, so it's incredibly precious[2]to her. I was so caught up in listening to the lovely[3]music that I dropped it! [4]I have got to fix this before Elizabeth comes back...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="125">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I managed to get the lid of the music box back on, but[0]when Elizabeth came in she was furious and kicked us [1]out of her room. We met her dad in the hall, and Janet[2]introduced us, then went to make some tea. Elizabeth[3]shouted at her dad through the door that she didn't[4]want to talk to him, so he talked to me for a bit...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="126">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>It turns out that Elizabeth's dad knows my dad from[0]way back. He stopped talking to me after saying[1]that Mom had been working on the EC Project. Janet[2]had made the tea, so I went downstairs and met[3]Elizabeth's dad on his way out. He asked me to tell [4]Janet that he'd gone...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="127">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to find Janet in the kitchen and told her that Mr[0]Alfred had left. We talked a bit about Elizabeth... Maybe[1]we could ask Tommy or Sam to talk to her about how[2]she really feels about her dad? Janet said that Elizabeth[3]was probably in a better mood by now, so I went to find[4]her...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="128">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I found Elizabeth in her dad's room. She's convinced he's[0]hiding things from her, and told me I couldn't possibly[1]understand. She was going through his desk and even[2]pulled out one of the drawers! It fell on the floor and as[3]soon as she saw what was in it, she got really upset[4]and ran out. What was she so shocked by? Let's see...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="129">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>There was a letter from someone called Kate inside[0]a drawer. I went back to the kitchen and Elizabeth[1]was crying... Janet accused me of doing something, so I[2]told her about what happened in Mr Alfred's room. She[3]said to go home, so I gave her the music player, ID card[4]and handkerchief and headed back to Dad's cottage...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="130">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got back to Dad's cottage, but Matt wasn't there! He[0]ran away - again![1]I looked upstairs and found a note from him saying he'd[2]gone to carry on looking for his dad. I can't believe he[3]went out on his own...[4]I'd better head out and find him...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="131">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I headed out to look for Matt and ran into Bob, but he [0]hadn't seen him anywhere. I kept looking and heard a[1]dog barking - it was Princess! She said that she'd help[2]me search for Matt, I think.[3] [4]Right, how are we going to find Matt?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="132">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I left Dad's cottage to look for Matt and ran into [0]Princess. I gave her something of his to smell, so the[1]two of us headed off to find him.[2] [3]I hope he hasn't run into Dan...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="133">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After finding Matt gone from the cottage, I headed out[0]with Princess to find him. When we got to the road by [1]the clock tower, Princess started barking - and there he[2]was! I told her what a good girl she was, and then went[3]to give Matt a good talking-to...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="134">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Although Matt promised his mom he'd never go to the[0]clock tower, he remembered something while trying to[1]think why she said that - he had seen her crying in front[2]of the clock tower door. We figured out that the design[3]on the door was the family crest of the guy who built it.[4]Whoa! Where did all those clouds come from?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="135">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While I was talking to Matt in front of the clock tower,[0]the sky suddenly went dark. We headed for the cottage,[1]but then the skies opened, so we sheltered at the[2]covered bridge for a bit. When the rain finally stopped,[3]we saw a rainbow! [4]But Matt doesn't look so good...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="136">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The moment we got back, Matt collapsed! I got him into[0]Dad's bed, but he's burning up... He absolutely refuses[1]to see a doctor because that would mean getting sent[2]back to his uncle's place. I looked everywhere for some[3]medicine or ice, but there was barely anything. [4]Someone around here must at least have some ice...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="137">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I thought I'd be able to get some ice at the diner, but[0]the ice machine was broken. I told Bob about Matt's [1]fever and he said that I should get some medicine from[2]a lady called Charlotte. [3] [4]He also said she's really cranky, so to be careful...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="138">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Bob told me about this old lady who has an amazing[0]fever medicine, so I went to find her. And she demands[1]I call her Mrs Graham. Okay... When I told her Bob[2]had sent me, she said she couldn't turn me away.[3] [4]I hope she gives me what I need...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="139">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I told Mrs Graham about Matt's fever and she gave me[0]her medicine recipe! She explained that you need to boil[1]red herbs in pure water, but I have to make it myself...[2]She lent me a mortar and pestle to crush the herbs and[3]said to get pure water from Lake Juliet. [4]Oh man, I hope I can really make this myself...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="140">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I found the red herb Mrs Graham told me about in her[0]greenhouse. She insisted that the recipe needs pure [1]water.[2] [3]Poor Matt, I hope he'll be okay...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="141">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>The medicine was finally ready, so I woke Matt up and[0]made him drink it. I told him that Mrs Graham had taught[1]me how to make it, and about her door having the same[2]crest as the clock tower. Matt remembered that he'd[3]been to Mrs Graham's house with his dad, and said that[4]he wanted to go and ask her about the clock tower...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="142">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I told Matt to rest and went to talk to Mrs Graham. I[0]heard shouting outside her house, and met a woman[1]walking away from it. She introduced herself as Lucy,[2]Mrs Graham's niece. She warned me that if I was going[3]to talk to Mrs Graham, I should never EVER mention her[4]daughter, Olivia, or the clock tower. Oh, great...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="143">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to see Mrs Graham and told her about Matt [0]searching for his dad and how I was trying to help him.[1]I asked her permission to look inside the clock tower.[2]After hearing why I wanted to, she said it was okay! [3] [4]And she told me about the Graham family's three keys...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="144">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mrs Graham told me three keys are needed to restart[0]the stopped clock in the tower. Mrs Graham lent me the[1]key to the shed where two of the keys are kept - the[2]sword key and moon key. They were attached to some[3]weird puzzle-scale thing, but I managed to balance it[4]and get them out. Now I need to find the third key...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="145">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mrs Graham told me that her daughter Olivia had the[0]third key, so I went to look in Olivia's room, which is[1]now a storage room. I found a book of photos of Lake [2]Juliet in a cupboard, and when I opened it there was an[3]old envelope inside. [4]I'd better show it to Mrs Graham...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="146">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I brought the old envelope I found in the store room to[0]Mrs Graham. Inside was the flower key, and a letter. It[1]was from Olivia, written five years ago when she eloped,[2]asking her mom to forgive her and her husband. I read[3]the letter to Mrs Graham, who just said that her [4]daughter never did understand her mother's feelings...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="147">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While he was looking for clues about his dad, Matt[0]came down with a fever and collapsed. Bob told me [1]about Mrs Graham and I went to see her to learn how to[2]make her medicine. Matt wanted to know more about the[3]clock tower, and Mrs Graham lent us the keys on the [4]condition that we make the bell ring again...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="148">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="149">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="150">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While he was out looking for clues about his dad, Matt[0]came down with a fever and collapsed. Bob told me [1]about Mrs Graham and I went to see her to learn how to[2]make her medicine. Matt wanted to know more about the[3]clock tower, and Mrs Graham lent us the keys on the [4]condition that we make the bell ring again...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="151">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got all three keys, but Mrs Graham doesn't know[0]how to restart the clock... She says that her dad should[1]have written something about how to start it in the[2]clock tower. Anyway, now I can get in and see for[3]myself![4]I'd better check on Matt first, though...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="152">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I got back to the cottage, Matt was already up.[0]I told him that the clock was stopped five years ago,[1]and about being allowed to borrow the three keys.[2]So, of course, he decided he had to come with me.[3] [4]Okay, if he really is better now...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="153">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got into the clock tower, but the stairs were broken![0]I looked around on the ground floor, found a hammer[1]and some nails, and used them to repair the stairs. Go [2]me! Now we can go up to the next floor.[3] [4]Matt doesn't seem too happy about it though...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="154">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After getting inside the clock tower with Matt and fixing[0]the stairs, we climbed up to the main clock room. As[1]soon as Matt got to that floor, he slumped down in a[2]corner and admitted he's afraid of heights.[3] [4]Fine, I'll just search the room by myself...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="155">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Leaving Matt and his fear of heights behind, I climbed[0]up to the very top of the tower to see the bell. The view[1]is incredible - you can see the whole of Lake Juliet! [2]Matt would have died on the spot![3] [4]I wonder what happened to that pillar, though...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="156">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Using the hints I found in the tower and the three keys,[0]I examined the machine in the main clock room and [1]managed to get it working again! All right![2]Matt was so fascinated by the clock, he forgot about [3]the height and got up to have a look at the mechanism.[4]He found that something had fallen down inside it...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="157">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I used the mop to get the puzzle box out from inside the[0]clock mechanism, but it won't open. Matt gave it to me[1]and said that he remembered playing with it in his dad's[2]office at Lake Juliet. He wasn't able to get in there[3]when he was here last year, but between the two of us[4]we should be able to find a way...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="158">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I left the clock tower with Matt, still carrying his puzzle[0]box, and the bell rang! And I remembered...hearing that[1]bell before, with Mom, and what she'd been doing. Then[2]I got a weird message from Dad on the DAS: "If you[3]don't want to wait, please go on home"?![4]Why did he send that? I'd better go see Dad...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="159">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We were on our way to the old Crusoe Resort offices, [0]just at the covered bridge, when we ran into Elizabeth.[1]She said she remembered hearing the bell with her [2]parents when she was a kid. She kind of apologised to[3]Matt about the music player, and admitted that she [4]was looking for attention...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="160">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While talking to Elizabeth, we realised that Princess[0]used to be her dog. So that's why Princess was getting[1]so excited about the handkerchief and music player...[2]Matt was desperate to get to his dad's office, but [3]before that I had to get back to Mrs Graham's place to[4]return the keys and tell her about restarting the clock...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="161">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>On the way to Mrs Graham's house we ran into Tommy,[0]who was looking for Elizabeth. He had been trying to[1]pressure her into taking their music seriously, and she[2]said she quit...but he doesn't want her to quit, and he [3]said that if any one of the three left, the band would[4]collapse. We left him to find her and carried on...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="162">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went to Mrs Graham's house with Matt, gave her back[0]the three keys and told her how I restarted the clock.[1]Matt thanked her for the medicine and Mrs Graham[2]told him that he'd been in her house before, years ago,[3]with his dad...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="163">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>At Mrs Graham's house, I returned the clock tower keys[0]and she told us about Matt's dad. I talked to her about [1]learning more about Mom since I came here, and showed[2]her Mom's kaleidoscope. Mrs Graham said that it's one[3]where you can change the chambers...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="164">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I took the chamber Mrs Graham had in her room and [0]used it to see some beautiful butterflies! Mrs Graham [1]said I could keep it, and she showed me a blanket that[2]always reminded her of her daughter Olivia. As soon as[3]I saw the blanket, I remembered that Mom had wrapped[4]me up in it too...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="165">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mrs Graham remembered something while talking to[0]Matt - his dad had that toy car with him when he [1]came to visit her years ago, the one we found in his [2]bag in the lake! Matt admitted that he really missed his[3]dad. And Mrs Graham showed us a shortcut to the old[4]Crusoe Resort offices at the back of her house...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="166">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mrs Graham let us go through her house to use a short[0]cut to the old Crusoe Resort offices. She told me that[1]I should look after Matt and not leave him alone, and[2]that if there were any problems I should send him back[3]to her place. I thanked her and we headed off for the[4]old Crusoe Resort offices...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="167">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>On the way to the old Crusoe Resort offices from Mrs[0]Graham's house, Matt asked me what I'd been talking[1]about with her before we left...but I said it was nothing.[2]We kept on going and before long Matt pointed out [3]some buildings ahead of us. The Crusoe Resort offices...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="168">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got to the old Crusoe Resort buildings, but the gate[0]was tied up with rope. Matt and I tried to find some way[1]in, and noticed a drainage tunnel by the side of the[2]fence. Matt got through the tunnel to the other side of[3]the fence and we both used a saw to cut through the [4]rope. We got through the gate and opened the door...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="169">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got into the old Crusoe Resort offices, and they[0]were in a state. There was a huge illustration of the [1]resort on the office wall, and we found the key to the[2]reference room in a cardboard box. Looks like Matt is[3]remembering more and more about his dad, too![4]Next stop, reference room...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="170">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We used the key we found in the office to get into the[0]reference room. It was full of lockers, and Matt [1]remembered hiding his sister Kelly's doll inside one of [2]them. I looked for the sticker Matt mentioned, [3]checked the locker shelf and found Kelly's doll...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="171">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I was handing the doll over to Matt when he suddenly[0]looked past me and said Kelly was there! I turned[1]around and there was a little girl standing behind me...[2]Kelly? She took her doll from Matt, smiled and then [3]faded away. Matt remembered how she died and blamed[4]himself, and I tried to convince him that he shouldn't...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="172">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We went back into the corridor, and ran straight into[0]Mr Smith! Matt said he recognised him. I asked him to tell[1]us about the incident from five years ago that he was[2]investigating, and he admitted that his name wasn't[3]John Smith at all. His real name is Greg Davis, and he's[4]looking for Matt's dad too...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="173">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mr Davis told us he was supposed to meet Matt's dad[0]in the clock tower five years ago to take his report on[1]the pollution of Lake Juliet... He said the report was [2]hidden in the puzzle box. We showed him the box, and[3]he gave us a note with the code to open it. Matt said[4]that if we opened the puzzle box he'd remember[5]something awful again, and he ran off...[6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="174">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I ran out of the old Crusoe Resort offices after Matt, [0]and found him standing on the path to Capulet Point.[1]He was ready to just give up, but I told him his [2]dad was still alive and we had to keep going! [3]Right, I'm going to use the note Mr Davis gave me to[4]try and open the box...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="175">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I used the note that Mr Davis gave us to open the [0]puzzle box, and found Michael Crusoe's report inside.[1]It said that JC Valley, not Crusoe Resort, was[2]responsible for the pollution of Lake Juliet.[3] [4]I decided to hand the report over to Mr Davis...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="176">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mr Davis promised to publicise the report and prove[0]that Crusoe Resort didn't pollute the lake. When he told[1]us about his informant inside JC Valley and Another O,[2]I showed him the JC Valley badge from the clock tower.[3]Then a message arrived from Dad - "Come to JC Valley[4]right away"...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="177">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After receiving a message from Dad asking me to come[0]to JC Valley straight away, I headed there with Matt.[1]When we went through the JC Valley car park, I saw the[2]same car that had been on the road when my bag was[3]stolen. And at the doors, I had another flashback about[4]Mom! I buzzed at the door, but there was no answer...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="178">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After getting the puzzle box from the clock tower[0]machinery with Matt, Mrs Graham showed us a [1]shortcut to the old Crusoe Resort offices. We met the [2]journalist Mr Davis there and gave him the report that[3]had been hidden inside the puzzle box. Then after I got[4]a weird message from Dad, I headed to JC Valley...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="179">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="180">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After getting the puzzle box from the clock tower[0]machinery with Matt, Mrs Graham showed us a [1]shortcut to the old Crusoe Resort offices. We met the [2]journalist Mr Davis there and gave him the report that[3]had been hidden inside the puzzle box. Then, after I got[4]a weird message from Dad, I headed to JC Valley...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="181">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina came to meet me instead of Dad. When she heard[0]that Matt was connected to Crusoe Resort, she started[1]going on about pollution...and said he couldn't come[2]into the lab with me. There's no way I can leave him out[3]here on his own! I told him to go back to Mrs Graham's[4]place and wait for me there...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="182">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina unlocked the front door of the offices and took me[0]to the B1F floor. Turns out most of the labs are actually[1]underground! She said the lab was built by Judd[2]Fitzgerald into the side of the lake shore. Dad's office is[3]on the B2F floor, but no non-scientists are allowed, so[4]I'm stuck in the meeting room...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="183">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As Gina left, I asked her about the security problems Dad[0]had mentioned on the phone but she said I must have it[1]wrong. Then I got a message from Dad: "Something's [2]happened at the lab, please take the TAS and go home [3]right away!" I realised I'd been locked in the meeting[4]room, but I used the TAS to unlock the door...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="184">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I got out of the meeting room and went to the front[0]desk. When I saw the JC Valley logo on the glass wall,[1]I remembered something about Mom and Ryan... Then I[2]saw Dad on a monitor in the room on the other side of[3]the glass wall. I tried to get in to contact him, but the [4]keypad was covered with some red stuff...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="185">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I had to clean up the keypad by the security room door[0]to have any chance of getting in, so I went looking and[1]found some cleaning spray in the meeting room. I used[2]it on the keypad, put in the code and got in![3] [4]Now to contact Dad...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="186">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dad was on the monitor in the security room behind[0]reception! I could see his name on the control panel on[1]the wall, so I tried pressing it and we were able to talk![2]He said he didn't send that message asking me to come[3]to JC Valley. He switched the DAS Connect function to[4]see the internal cameras - and then he was cut off...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="187">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Worried sick about what had happened to Dad, I found[0]Mike Tyler's name on the Video Conference panel. That's[1]the guy giving information to Mr Davis! I called and told[2]him I was Richard Robins' daughter and that something[3]had happened to my dad and he needs help![4]Mike said he'd try to contact Dad and hung up...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="188">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>While I was worrying over what was happening to Dad,[0]Mike called me back on the VC system. He said he [1]couldn't contact Dad so he'd come to get me from the[2]security room. He couldn't believe it when he saw the[3]damaged control panel. I told him what had happened[4]since I got to JC Valley...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="189">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When Mike came to the security room, I told him about[0]Gina locking me in the meeting room - but he said there[1]was no way she'd do that. He explained the Connect[2]function to me. Turns out Dad used it to monitor the lab[3]security system.[4]Then he told me to go on ahead to his office...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="190">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I waited in Mike's office while he finished checking out [0]the security room. He came back and said there was a[1]lot of damage. It was probably dangerous for me to[2]wander randomly around the lab, so he told me to stay[3]in his room while he went to check Dad's office...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="191">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When Mike got back from the security room, he said it [0]was dangerous for me to wander around the lab, so I[1]had to wait in his office while he went to check on Dad.[2]I knew I should wait for Mike, but I was so worried about[3]Dad that I tried to leave to find him myself. Just as I[4]was about to leave, the VC rang...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="192">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I answered the VC in Mike's office, the real Gina -[0]the one I saw on the name tag - appeared on the screen.[1]While I was talking to her, the fake Gina came into the[2]room! She ran off, but Gina recognised her as Sofia.[3]Gina said that we should meet up in Dad's office.[4]I'm so worried about him...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="193">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I headed to the B2F floor to meet up with the real Gina[0]after talking to her on the VC. As I got out of the[1]elevator, I saw Sofia run through a security shutter[2]that closed behind her! Wait...that's her![3]That's the woman who stole my bag at the bus stop![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="194">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I managed to get to the B2F floor and saw Sofia run[0]through one of the security shutters and close it after[1]her. I noticed a gap at the bottom and peeked through -[2]Dad's name tag was on the floor on the other side![3] [4]What's Dad's name tag doing there...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="195">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I used the TAS to get into Dad's office, I found[0]Mike collapsed on the floor! I woke him up, but he just[1]muttered something about an e-mail and fell[2]unconscious again. I had a look at the e-mail on Dad's[3]computer, and it said that he knows Sofia was up to[4]something! I could try to get into her room...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="196">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I remembered that there's a card lock on the other[0]side of the shutter! I used the TAS through the gap at[1]the bottom of the shutter to open it. It was horribly[2]complicated with a mirror and changing the angle with[3]a fishing rod...but I did it! I opened the shutter and got[4]Dad's name tag. Dad, please be okay...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="197">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I got to Sofia's room, Gina was collapsed inside![0]Then Sofia, who had pretended to be Gina, turned up.[1]She admitted she was Sofia, told me to behave until[2]she'd finished what she was doing...and pulled out a[3]stun gun! She used it to destroy the card lock and left.[4]What am I going to do? First, try to wake up Gina...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="198">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After I got into Sofia's room and found Gina collapsed[0]inside, Sofia arrived and locked us both in! When Gina[1]came around, I asked her what had happened to Dad.[2] [3]Gina started to tell me what Dad meant when he said[4]he'd found out who it was and that it was Sofia...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="199">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I finally managed to wake Gina up, and told her Mike[0]had been attacked as well. She said that Dad had[1]discovered Sofia was leaking confidential information.[2]When Gina felt a bit better, we printed out proof of[3]what Sofia was doing from her computer.[4]Right, let's get out of here...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="200">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>As Gina and I were locked in the room, we had to use [0]the VC to call for help. When we called Dad's office, [1]Mike was there! The sound was broken on our end, so[2]he couldn't hear us, but I managed to mime enough[3]that he knew we needed help. He told us about the [4]emergency door release, and we unlocked the door...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="201">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We got out of Sofia's office and met up with Mike. He [0]told us to wait there while he scouted out the rest of[1]the building. When he left, we decided to go back to [2]Gina's office to try to decode Sofia's e-mail...[3]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="202">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>We went back to Gina's office and tried to crack Sofia's[0]coded e-mail. Gina tried to use a scanner pen to do it,[1]but her right arm hurt so much that I used it for her. [2]She told me how to do it, so here I go...let's crack this[3]code![4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="203">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina came to pick me up at the front door of JC Valley.[0]Then she took me to the meeting room and locked me in![1]I got out and called Dad over the VC, but we got cut off.[2]I got in touch with Mike, and found out that the woman[3]I thought was Gina was actually Sofia! Gina and I were[4]locked in Sofia's office, but we managed to get out...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="204">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="205">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="206">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="207">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="208">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="209">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="210">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina came to pick me up at the front door of JC Valley.[0]Then she took me to the meeting room and locked me in![1]I got out and called Dad over the VC, but we got cut off.[2]I got in touch with Mike, and found out that the woman[3]I thought was Gina was actually Sofia! Gina and I were[4]locked in Sofia's office, but we managed to get out...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="211">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Gina said she needed to report to the director that[0]Sofia was leaking information, but he wouldn't really[1]believe us right away. Then Ryan called on the VC. Gina[2]and I explained everything that had happened in the lab.[3] [4]Now he wants us to come to his office...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="212">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ryan opened the shutter beyond Sofia's office and came[0]to meet us. Gina told him she was working with Dad to[1]find the mole, and they'd found out it was Sofia. Gina[2]went off to get Mike and check the exit and entry data.[3] [4]Now I have to go with Ryan into his office...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="213">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ryan brought me into his office. He was really surprised[0]that I was in the lab at all! I said that I'd got a message[1]from Dad but Dad said he didn't send it, and that[2]Sofia's a bad person. But Ryan didn't believe me, he[3]said he thinks Dad's just testing me.[4]Testing me? What's that supposed to mean?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="214">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Ryan got a call from the director, Elizabeth's dad, and[0]said he'd report everything about Dad and Sofia. He left[1]me on my own, locking the door behind him so I'd be[2]safe in here.[3]I was just starting to get paranoid again when the[4]VC rang...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="215">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I was on my own in Ryan's office when the VC rang. It[0]was Dad! He told me not to give the TAS to anyone,[1]and that he was locked in the control room. He said to[2]go and meet Elizabeth's dad, and not to trust Ryan.[3]Then he got cut off...[4]Dad, what's going on here?![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="216">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I didn't know what to do after the VC call from Dad, but[0]I remembered what Matt said and I swore again that I'd[1]go and find Dad. So I used the TAS to get out of Ryan's[2]office.[3] [4]I have to go tell Mr Alfred where Dad is![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="217">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I unlocked the door of Ryan's office and headed for[0]Elizabeth's dad's office. The door was locked, so I[1]used the TAS to open it and went in.[2] [3]Sofia was in the room - and she wanted to know how I[4]got in. I couldn't tell her about the TAS...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="218">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Sofia said she didn't know anything about Dad, and all[0]she was after was info on the EC Project. And even[1]worse, Ryan's her partner! He wants to get some[2]device working again in the lab...[3]Sofia told me about Another, and in exchange I promised[4]not to leave the room until I find a secret compartment...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="219">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>After Sofia left, I looked around the room for the[0]secret compartment. I was able to find it using Judd's[1]memoirs and a celestial globe. Inside was a small case[2]with an imprint the same shape as Mom's pendant.[3] [4]Then Elizabeth's dad burst into the room...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="220">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When I opened the secret compartment and found the[0]little case, Elizabeth's dad came in. He was surprised to[1]see me, but told me about 13 years ago and that Mom's[2]pendant has part of her memories in it. Then we got[3]a call from Ryan. He's starting experiments with[4]Another. I have to get down to that lab![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="221">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mr Alfred and I ran down to the Another lab, where[0]Ryan was doing an experiment with Another...on Dad![1]The door was locked with a biometric sensor, and Mr[2]Alfred's data had been removed by Ryan. But my data[3]from 13 years ago should still be in there.[4]Right, I'll use my handprint to unlock the door...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="222">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went into the Another lab and found Dad inside the[0]unit. I asked Ryan not to delete Dad's memories, and he [1]said he'd stop the experiment if I go to Dad's office, find[2]a box of Mom's and bring what I find inside to him.[3]I can't let Dad lose his memories, I value him thinking[4]about me too much. I have to save him...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="223">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went looking for the box in Dad's office. I looked in a[0]drawer under lots of chocolate bars and found the box[1]and a kaleidoscope chamber. I plugged the thing from[2]inside the box into the TAS, and I heard Mom's voice![3]"Ashley..." She told me why she created the TAS.[4]I need to get back to the lab, now![5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="224">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went with Gina to explain everything to Ryan. I was so[0]happy someone was finally doing something, but then[1]Dad called me over the VC and said not to trust Ryan![2]Then Sofia told me what Ryan was really trying to do...[3]and he did an experiment on Dad using Another![4]Dad looks really out of it, what did Ryan do to him?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="225">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="226">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="227">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="228">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="229">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="230">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="231">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="232">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="233">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="234">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="235">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="236">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="237">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="238">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="239">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="240">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I went with Gina to explain everything to Ryan. I was so[0]happy someone was finally doing something, but then[1]Dad called me over the VC and said not to trust Ryan![2]Then Sofia told me what Ryan was really trying to do...[3]and he did an experiment on Dad using Another![4]Dad looks really out of it, what did Ryan do to him?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="241">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When Dad came out of Another, he'd forgotten all about[0]me! I gave Ryan the TAS upgrade module, but he said[1]it wasn't the system unlock device he expected it to be.[2]Then when I asked him to put Dad's memories back,[3]he told me he wanted me to take part in a memory[4]overwrite experiment...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="242">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I took part in Ryan's experiment, but I didn't lose any[0]of my memories. I told Ryan I'd use the TAS to bring[1]back Dad's memories, but when Ryan heard I had Mom's[2]device, he pointed a gun at me! Dad jumped out and[3]saved me, but Mr Alfred tried to stop Ryan and he got[4]shot instead! Now he's injured.[5]I have to use the TAS to restore Dad's memories...[6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="243">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Mr Alfred told me to put the TAS in the control panel so[0]I could bring back Dad's memories. I went into the[1]control room, and Mr Alfred told Dad to get into[2]Another. I put the TAS in the control panel like he said,[3]and then the system booted up...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="244">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I'm so glad Dad got his memories back...[0]Dad brought out a laptop from the control room. As[1]soon as I saw it, I remembered Mom writing something[2]on it. Mr Alfred said Judd used to use it, and Mom [3]might have put some sort of security lock on it.[4]How do I unlock it?[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="245">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>I was able to unlock the laptop thanks to the flashback[0]I had after looking at it. Judd had left some sort of[1]final speech on it, and we found out that he was[2]actually Ryan's dad! Mr Alfred was worried about Ryan,[3]so Dad and I decided to go after him...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="246">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Before we went after Ryan, I called Gina on the VC so[0]she could get help for Mr Alfred. Mike was there with[1]her.[2] [3]Now Dad and I are going after Ryan...[4]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="247">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>Dad and I went down in an elevator and came out into[0]some kind of underground tunnel. We followed Ryan[1]down the tunnel, but he had locked the exit.[2]The other way out was blocked off by rocks... But[3]Dad was really cool! He moved the rocks out of the way[4]so we could get out.[5]Where's Ryan gone now?[6]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="248">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When we came out of the cave, Dad told me about a[0]spring in the forest. It's the water source for Lake[1]Juliet. He was pretty convinced that the pure water from[2]the spring would make the lake clean again. I really hope[3]it does...[4]Anyway, we have to go after Ryan...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="249">
    <Commands>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>Cg==</Command>
      <Command>CgA=</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>When we arrived at the lake there was a small wharf.[0]Ryan was out in a boat heading for some small island[1]on the lake. We hopped on a boat and went after him.[2]On the boat, Dad told me he came to JC Valley to find[3]out who was really responsible for Mom's death.[4]And now we've just reached the island...[5]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="250">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="251">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="252">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="253">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="254">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="255">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="256">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="257">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="258">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="259">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="260">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="261">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="262">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="263">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="264">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="265">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="266">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="267">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="268">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="269">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AAAAAA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Comments />
</Session>