<Session title="PUZZLE_TXT_003.MESS">
  <Sentence id="0">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>27 March 2007

Ashley really is the most precious thing in
my life. But what does she really think
about me now? How can I be what she needs
from a father?
When I left Blood Edward Island, I wanted 
nothing more than to make up for all the time
we'd been apart. But now here I am, separated
from her once again.
Even if she knew everything about why I'm
doing this, would she forgive me?[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="1">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>13 May 2007

It's been a year since I received that strange,
anonymous e-mail. At first I thought it was
some kind of sick joke, but as the days go by
I find myself thinking about it more and more.
If what it says is true...
Sayoko, what should I do?
It hurts so much every time I think about
you...[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="2">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>20 July 2007

I got hold of a water testing kit, and took
samples from different places around the lake.
What Dan feared has come true - the
pollution that plagued Lake Juliet five years 
ago has returned.
But why?[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Sentence id="3">
    <Commands>
      <Command>AA==</Command>
    </Commands>
    <Original>2 August 2007

Sayoko...
Not a single night goes by when I don't think
of you. And it's only when I think of you that
I can forget that you're not with me any more.

Sayoko, Ashley looks so much like you.
Especially her eyes - whenever I see them, I
remember the day we first met. And then I
realise...your last act was to protect Ashley.
What I have to do now is make sure she's
happy.[0]</Original>
    <Translation>
    </Translation>
  </Sentence>
  <Comments />
</Session>